<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Swift on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/tags/swift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Swift on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://perlweeklychallenge.org/tags/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 018&amp;rdquo; by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like APL, Awk, Basic, Bash, Bc, Befunge, Brainfuck, C, Chef, Cobol, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Elm, Erlang, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, Haskell, HTML, Idris, Java, JavaScript, Kotlin, Lisp, Lua, Mumps, Node, OCaml, Ook, Pascal, PHP, Python, Postscript, Prolog, R, Ruby, Rust, Scala, SQL, Swift, Tcl and XSLT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #075</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-075/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-075/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINE The week #075 tasks turned out to be a lot trickier than expected. Generally Task #1 is meant for beginners only but this time it was not the case. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t my plan when I proposed the task. I thought couple of for-loops and job done. But when I actually started working on the task, I realised it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as I thought initially. But the good thing is, I got to know about Dynamic Programming (DP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #074</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-074/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-074/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINE Ever since I started doing Swift, I find myself too busy again with my weekly video sessions on top of all.
I need to re-visit my time management chart, may be?
Having said that, I get excited by the doing task in a new language. I wanted to do it in Java to refresh my memory. But couldn&amp;rsquo;t find time for it as I am editing the next week Perl Weekly newsletter also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #073</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-073/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-073/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINE Happy Independence Day to all my fellow Indians This week tasks are once again fun and challenging. Keeping the balance is very difficult, I must admit.
 but I am trying &amp;hellip;
 For the first time, I have joined the private Early Bird Club and taking the advantage of doing the challenge before the launch. I am not sure, if you noticed, this I shared by solutions before lunch time on day one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #072</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-072/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-072/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINE No Linked List related task this week?
I am glad, this week focus was more Array/List related. Technical speaking Array and List aren&amp;rsquo;t the same in Perl. I must admit until I read the article by brian d foy, I thought they were the same. As the famous saying, you learn something new every day.
Both the tasks, this week were not terribly difficult. I noticed many members of Team PWC attempted other languages because they finished the tasks in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>