<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 18, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 17 | Day 18 |  The gift is presented by Lubos Kolouch. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 233. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1 - Similar Words  Introduction Programming often presents challenges that may seem trivial at first glance, but when delved into, bring out intriguing nuances. One such problem is identifying words with similar character sets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 |  Welcome to our 5th Advent Calendar. We have had enormous amount of blog post shared by Team PWC members. In this edition of Advent Calendar, we are going to pick some of the best creative work by the expert members of Team PWC.                         MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 247</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-247/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-247/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 248</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-248/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Shortest Distance 10. TASK #2: Submatrix Sum HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #248 of The Weekly Challenge.
Happy Holiday season to Team PWC members. I would like to take this opportunity to thank each member for the support and encouragement. With new year just couple of weeks behind, let us all enjoy the holiday break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 17, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-17/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 16 | Day 17 | Day 18 |  The gift is presented by Luca Ferrari. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 228. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Sums and Swaps  PWC 228 - Task 1 - Raku Implementation You are given an array of integers. Write a script to find out the sum of unique elements in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 16, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 15 | Day 16 | Day 17 |  The gift is presented by Andrew Shitov. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 227. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Counting Fridays the 13th in Raku  The Task 1 of the Weekly Challenge 227 is the following:
You are given a year number in the range 1753 to 9999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 15, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 14 | Day 15 | Day 16 |  The gift is presented by Adam Russell. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 225. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Sentenced To Compute Differences  The examples used here are from the weekly challenge problem statement and demonstrate the working solution.
Part 1 You are given a list of sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 14, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 13 | Day 14 | Day 15 |  The gift is presented by Roger Bell_West. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 223. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Counting Boxes  Task 1: Count Primes You are given a positive integer, $n. Write a script to find the total count of primes less than or equal to the given integer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 13, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-13/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 12 | Day 13 | Day 14 |  The gift is presented by Arne Sommer. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 222. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Raku Members  Challenge #222.1: Matching Members You are given a list of positive integers, @ints. Write a script to find the total matching members after sorting the list increasing order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>