<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 25, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-25/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 24 | Day 25 |  The gift is presented by Mohammad Sajid Anwar. Today I am looking back at the Year 2024 performance as a whole.
 The Weekly Challenge: REVIEW 2024   SPONSORS CHAMPIONS REVIEWERS REGULAR CONTRIBUTORS GUEST CONTRIBUTORS CONTRIBUTIONS GUEST LANGUAGES GITHUB REPOSITORY   Merry Christmas everyone !!!
Being a practice muslim, I don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate Christmas but I do wish all my friends (Christian by faith) on this occassion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 24, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-24/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 23 | Day 24 | Day 25 |  The gift is presented by Jaldhar H. Vyas. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 299. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Perl Weekly Challenge: Week 299  Challenge #1: Replace Words You are given an array of words and a sentence. Write a script to replace all words in the given sentence that start with any of the words in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 23, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 22 | Day 23 | Day 24 |  The gift is presented by Luca Ferrari. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 298. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Perl Weekly Challenge 298  This post presents my solutions to the Perl Weekly Challenge 298.
I keep doing the Perl Weekly Challenge in order to mantain my coding skills in good shape, as well as in order to learn new things, with particular regard to Raku, a language that I love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 300</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-300/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 301</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-301/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-301/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Largest Number 10. TASK #2: Hamming Distance HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #301 of The Weekly Challenge.
Last week, I noticed a slight jump in contributions by Team PWC members. Well done team.
Ryan Thompson didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss the celebration either. So here we have his contributions in Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 22, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-22/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 21 | Day 22 | Day 23 |  The gift is presented by Packy Anderson. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 286. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Spammer Game  For some reason, my brain saw “Order Game” and I thought “Circle Game“. Perhaps because my wife and I watched a Joni Mitchell documentary last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 21, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-21/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 20 | Day 21 | Day 22 |  The gift is presented by Bruce Gray. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 277. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Strength Uncombined  Task #1: Count Common Given two arrays of strings, return the count of words that appears in both arrays exactly once.  Observations:  The task specifies two input arrays, but is easier to express once we allow for unlimited input arrays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 20, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 19 | Day 20 | Day 21 |  The gift is presented by BarrOff. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 260. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Occurrences with BQN  Task #1: Unique Occurrences You are given an array of integers, @ints. Write a script to return 1 if the number of occurrences of each value in the given array is unique or 0 otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 19, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-19/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 18 | Day 19 | Day 20 |  The gift is presented by David Ferrone. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 285. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Lost Connections and Making Changes  Task #1: No Connection Given a list of routes, find the destination with no outgoing connection. For example, given [B, C] [D, B] [C, A] we have routes B -&amp;gt; C -&amp;gt; A D -&amp;gt; B -&amp;gt; C -&amp;gt; A C -&amp;gt; A Output: A  I make two lists, in-routes and out-routes, and then I see if there is an out that is not also an in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>