<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 4, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 3 | Day 4 |  The gift is presented by Dave Jacoby. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 209. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Give A Little Bit  Welcome to Weekly Challenge #209. I can’t do another HTTP.cats pic because 209 is not an assigned HTTP response code, but it is the area code for a huge part of central California, including Calaveras county, made famous by Mark Twain and The Celebrated Jumping Frog of Calaveras County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 |  Welcome to our 5th Advent Calendar. We have had enormous amount of blog post shared by Team PWC members. In this edition of Advent Calendar, we are going to pick some of the best creative work by the expert members of Team PWC.                         MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 3, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 2 | Day 3 | Day 4 |  The gift is presented by James Smith. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 208. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1: Minimum Index Sum  You are given two arrays of strings. Write a script to find out all common strings in the given two arrays with minimum index sum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 2, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 1 | Day 2 | Day 3 |  The gift is presented by Bob Lied. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 206. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task : Array Pairings  Perl Weekly Challenge number 206 has a task called &amp;quot;Array Pairings&amp;quot; to solve:
You are given an array of integers having even number of elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 1, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 1 | Day 2 |  The gift is presented by Laurent Rosenfeld. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 205. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task #1: Third Highest  You are given an array of integers. Write a script to find out the Third Highest if found otherwise return the maximum. Example 1 Input: @array = (5,3,4) Output: 3 First highest is 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 244</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-244/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-244/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 245</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-245/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-245/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Sort Language 10. TASK #2: Largest of Three HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #245 of The Weekly Challenge.
I am sure you all have noticed the popularity of Python among the team members. It is the top most loved programming language after Perl and Raku.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 243</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-243/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-243/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 244</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-244/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-244/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Count Smaller 10. TASK #2: Group Hero HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #244 of The Weekly Challenge.
Just a gentle reminder that we would be preparing Advent Calendar 2023 very soon. If you want any of your past blog to be part of this year Advent Calendar then please do share your blog post link to perlweeklychallenge@yahoo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>