<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>git show ...</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-show/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  git show &amp;hellip; I would say, git show, is the most used git command in the life of a programmer after git commit.
Believe it or not, we do so many commits in a day and we peek into a commit if we are investigating an issue.
This is what we do actually: git show &amp;lt;commit_id&amp;gt;, to be precise.
Yeah, so we all know that, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of this post?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 312</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-312/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 313</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-313/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Broken Keys 10. TASK #2: Reverse Letters HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #313 of The Weekly Challenge.
Thank you, Kaushik, for back to back contributions in Perl and blog post.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if noticed this, there is a drop in Raku contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git bisect ...</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-bisect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-bisect/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  git bisect &amp;hellip; If you lead life of a programmer, no matter what language you use, you must have used one of the many versioning systems.
CVS was my first introduction to the life saving tool. I think it was early 2000s time period.
I remember a real life incident, I was working as a consultant for a web portal firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promise in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/promise-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/promise-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Promise in Perl  Few days ago, I blogged about Future in Perl where I mentioned Future aka Promise.
In this post, I would replicate the behaviour using CPAN modules: Promise::ES6 and AE.
Since Perl believes in the philosophy of TMTOWTDI, so let&amp;rsquo;s implement the most basic pattern of Promiseas below:
fetch() .then(process) .then(save) .then(display) .catch(error);  #!/usr/bin/env perl use v5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientist in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/scientist-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/scientist-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Scientist in Perl  It was in the year 2017, I found out about the CPAN module Scientist and guess what?
It turned out be created by a very dear friend of mine, Lance Wicks.
I submitted few pull requests, mostly low hanging fruits, during that period and it was kindly accepted and merged.
You might ask me, what is Scientist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Extraction in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/extraction-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/extraction-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Text Extraction in Perl  I have always been fascinated about image processing but never got my head around it.
Even today, I barely know anything about it.
Text extraction from image is something, I always wanted to try but never managed to do it successfully.
I tried first in Perl but when I failed in my attempt then I tried in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/future-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/future-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Future in Perl  Recently I have been playing with Concurrent and Parallel Programming in Perl.
It is something that I don&amp;rsquo;t get to do on daily basis.
Having said this exercise, gave me an opportunity to try key features and document for future reference.
In the series, today I am talking about Futures in my favourite programming language Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 311</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-311/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>