<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 25, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-25/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 24 | Day 25 |  The gift is presented by Cheok-Yin Fung. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 246. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 CY&amp;rsquo;s Take on The Weekly Challenge #246 ‐ Uniqueness  Task 1: 6 out of 49 Instead of picking out the balls from a box, we can imagine we line up a set of balls labelled 1, 2, 3 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 |  Welcome to our 5th Advent Calendar. We have had enormous amount of blog post shared by Team PWC members. In this edition of Advent Calendar, we are going to pick some of the best creative work by the expert members of Team PWC.                         MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 248</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-248/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 249</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-249/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-249/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Equal Pairs 10. TASK #2: DI String Match HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #249 of The Weekly Challenge.
Merry Christmas everyone !!!
I wish Team PWC members great success in everything they do.
I pray new year brings good luck to all.
Please do enjoy quality time with your family and loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 24, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-24/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 23 | Day 24 | Day 25 |  The gift is presented by Jorg Sommrey. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 243. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Count the Pairs on the Floor  Task 1: Reverse Pairs You are given an array of integers. Write a script to return the number of reverse pairs in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 23, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 22 | Day 23 | Day 24 |  The gift is presented by Ian Rifkin. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 240. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 A.A.B.A. (Acronym And Build Array)  Task 1: Acronym You are given an array of strings and a check string. Write a script to find out if the check string is the acronym of the words in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 22, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-22/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 21 | Day 22 | Day 23 |  The gift is presented by Augie De Blieck Jr.. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 238. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 The Weekly Challenge began as a Perl-focused exercise but has since expanded to let any and all languages in. It’s still mostly Perl, but I’ll be using it as an avenue to explore other languages, as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 21, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-21/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 20 | Day 21 | Day 22 |  The gift is presented by Yves Orton. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 237. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Seize The Day - Simple Rules The Day  My solution was based on using Time::Local to compute the epoch for noon on the first day of the month, and then stepping forward by day until the required day of week has been found, and then stepping forward by week until the required repetition of that day has been found, or we ran off the end of the calender month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 20, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 19 | Day 20 | Day 21 |  The gift is presented by Jaldhar H. Vyas. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 235. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Challenge 1: Remove One  You are given an array of integers. Write a script to find out if removing ONLY one integer makes it strictly increasing order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>