<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry at Bash</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/angry-at-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/angry-at-bash/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Angry at Bash  I have noticed a very weird behavior in bash recently that I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen in my entire career of over two and a half decades.
Look at this one line to create a text file:
$ echo &amp;#34;Hello World!!&amp;#34; &amp;gt; hello.txt 
This is what one do as a quick win, right?
What would you expect?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub meets GitLab</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-meets-gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-meets-gitlab/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.          GitHub meets GitLab  Recently at work, I had to work with a codebase that resides in GitLab.
I am a die-hard GitHub user and never considered GitLab for any one of my pet projects.
All my open-source work is public on GitHub.
That said, I created an account, @manwar, on GitLab as a protest when Microsoft took over GitHub, but I never used it as much as GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-to-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-to-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.                  Welcome to Perl  1. Introduction 2. The Shebang 3. Command Interpretation 4. Interpreter Initialisation 5. File Handling 6. Lexical Analysis 7. Bytecode Generation 8. Runtime Execution 9. Output 10. Termination 11. Returns Control Introduction  Are you new to Perl?
If so, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure, you&amp;rsquo;d want to write your first Hello World program in Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subroutine Signatures in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/subroutine-signatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/subroutine-signatures/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.                  Subroutine Signatures in Perl  NOTE: All credit for this article goes to the book Perl New Features by brian d foy.
Have you ever missed subroutine signatures in Perl?
I missed it a lot when I used to program in Java.
Then when Raku introduced its coolest subroutine signatures, I started wondering, when would Perl get subroutine signatures?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/random-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/random-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.                  Environment variable PERL_RAND_SEED in Perl v5.38  NOTE: All credit for this article goes to the book Perl New Features by brian d foy.
How many of you have generated random numbers in Perl?
I guess almost everyone.
Let me ask another question: What function do you use to generate random numbers in Perl?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Regex</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-regex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-regex/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.                  Special variable ${^LAST_SUCCESSFUL_PATTERN} in Perl v5.38  NOTE: All credit for this article goes to the book Perl New Features by brian d foy.
I have been following the Perl releases closely for some time now. I don&amp;rsquo;t just track the maintenance releases but also the development releases, which comes more frequently with smaller updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 313</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-313/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 314</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-314/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Equal Strings 10. TASK #2: Sort Column HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #314 of The Weekly Challenge.
We have a new member, Darren Yates, joining Team PWC.
Welcome aboard! I hope you find our group fun and entertaining while also surprising you with its magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform with Docker</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Terraform with Docker  1. Introduction 2. Objectives 3. What is Terraform? 4. Why Terraform? 5. Terraform Configuration File 6. Terraform Workflow 7. Setup 8. Action 9. Cleanup Introduction  A few days ago, I shared my story about creating a Docker image for The Weekly Challenge website in this blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>