<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 172</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-172/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 173</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-173/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Esthetic Number 10. TASK #2: Sylvester&amp;rsquo;s sequence HEADLINES  Welcome to Week #173 of the weekly challenge.
I nominate, Ryan Thompson for the signed copy of Learning Perl, 8th edition by brian d foy. Next week, we are going to have one more nomination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colin Crain › Perl Weekly Review #166</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-166/</guid>
      <description>( &amp;hellip;continues from previous week. )
Welcome to the Perl review pages for Week 166 of The Weekly Challenge! Here we will take the time to discuss the submissions offered up by the team, factor out some common methodologies that came up in those solutions, and highlight some of the unique approaches and unusual code created.
 ●︎ Why do we do these challenges? I suppose any reasonable answer to that question would be from a field as wide ranging and varied as the people who choose to join the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Elixir, Elm, Erlang, Excel VBA, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Miranda, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 171</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-171/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-171/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 172</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-172/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Prime Partition 10. TASK #2: Five-number Summary HEADLINES  Welcome to Week #172 of the weekly challenge.
Today is the first Monday of the month and time to announce the champion. Proud to declare PokGoPun as our next champion. He is relatively new to the Team PWC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: May 2022</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2022-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2022-05/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about Robert Ransbottom. Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we spoke to Matthew Neleigh, the winner of April 2022.
Today we are talking to Robert Ransbottom, the winner of May 2022 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Robert: I read most of a brief computing-101-ish book at a book store one afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test::Excel</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/test-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/test-excel/</guid>
      <description>My first contribution to CPAN was Test::Excel. It was initiated as we had requirement for such at work at that time.
It has gone through many changes, thanks to all for reporting issues and providing patches..
It even got space as topic for Day 18 in Perl Advent Calendar 2018.
It was a proud moment when a collegue of mine at work requested help with Test::Excel as it was not behaving as per her requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Question ???</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-question/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I received an email from someone who appears to be Perl hacker and asked me a question.
 First, I feel honoured that somebody thinks I am capable to answer this question.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t want quick reply to the email. Instead, I decided to write a short blog post and share with other Perl hackers, just in case.
I have seen both styles and I believe it is just a matter of personal choice and style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 1000 days</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/1000-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/1000-days/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. UPDATES 3. SPONSORS 4. PLAN 5. CHAMPIONS HEADLINES  We all know, The Weekly Challenge a.k.a Perl Weekly Challenge started on 25th March 2019. I must confess I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect it to last this long. What worked in our favour is that we instantly found handful core supporters, who not only took part in the weekly challenge regularly but also started spreading the word.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>