<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/cve-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/cve-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  1. What&amp;rsquo;s CVE? 2. Key Features 3. How CVE works? 4. Why CVE matters? 5. How to audit? 6. Why recreate CVEs? 7. Known CVEs 8. Recreate CVEs 9. Further Sources  What&amp;rsquo;s CVE?  CVE stands for Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures.
It is a publicly available dictionary of known cybersecurity vulnerabilities and exposures.
It provides a standardised way to identify and track security issues in software and hardware systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 315</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-315/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-315/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 316</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-316/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Circular 10. TASK #2: Subsequence HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #316 of The Weekly Challenge.
Today is the first Monday of the month and it&amp;rsquo;s time to declare the next champion!
With great pride, I announce, Eric Cheung, as the Champion of the Month for March 2025.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git refs ...</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-refs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-refs/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.             1. Introduction 2. Types of refs 3. List refs 4. Useful Commands 5. HEAD shortcuts 6. Types of HEAD 7. trunk in Git 8. Git Remotes 9. Types of Remote refs Introduction  Today is such a fine and sunny Sunday morning to do some brain dumping and share it with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 314</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-314/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 315</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-315/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-315/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Find Words 10. TASK #2: Find Third HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #315 of The Weekly Challenge.
Let&amp;rsquo;s all welcome, Ashwin Shenoy, from India to Team PWC. Thanks Ashwin for your first contributions in Dart and Python.
Thank you, E. Choroba, for getting back to me with PayPal details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angry at Bash</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/angry-at-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/angry-at-bash/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Angry at Bash  I have noticed a very weird behavior in bash recently that I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen in my entire career of over two and a half decades.
Look at this one line to create a text file:
$ echo &amp;#34;Hello World!!&amp;#34; &amp;gt; hello.txt 
This is what one does as a quick win, right?
What would you expect?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub meets GitLab</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-meets-gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-meets-gitlab/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            GitHub meets GitLab  Recently at work, I had to work with a codebase that resides in GitLab.
I am a die-hard GitHub user and never considered GitLab for any one of my pet projects.
All my open-source work is public on GitHub.
That said, I created an account, @manwar, on GitLab as a protest when Microsoft took over GitHub, but I never used it as much as GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-to-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-to-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.                  Welcome to Perl  1. Introduction 2. The Shebang 3. Command Interpretation 4. Interpreter Initialisation 5. File Handling 6. Lexical Analysis 7. Bytecode Generation 8. Runtime Execution 9. Output 10. Termination 11. Returns Control Introduction  Are you new to Perl?
If so, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure, you&amp;rsquo;d want to write your first Hello World program in Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>