<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: December 2022</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2022-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2022-12/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about Ali Moradi Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we declared Bruce Gray, the winner of November 2022.
Today we are talking to Ali Moradi, the winner of December 2022 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Ali: I first got interested in programming and programming languages by translating some Python articles to Persian for a website when I was in secondary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: April 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-04/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about Thomas Kohler Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we declared David Ferrone, the winner of March 2023.
Today we are talking to Thomas Kohler, the winner of April 2023 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Thomas: Growing up on a farm, I learned a lot to improvise: When a machine was broken, we fixed it with whatever was available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 214</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-214/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 215</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-215/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Odd one Out 10. TASK #2: Number Placement HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #215 of The Weekly Challenge.
Today is the first Monday of the month and time to declare the next champion. With great pride, we announce Thomas Kohler as our next champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: February 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-02/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about Solathian Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we declared Bob Lied, the winner of January 2023.
Today we are talking to Solathian, the winner of February 2023 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Solathian: I&amp;rsquo;m an Electrical Egineer working as an embedded SW developer in the Automotive industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: March 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-03/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about David Ferrone Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we spoke to Solathian, the winner of February 2023.
Today we are talking to David Ferrone, the winner of March 2023 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
David: We had a PC in the house around 1992, I was eight and it ended up in my bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 213</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-213/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 214</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-214/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Rank Score 10. TASK #2: Collect Points HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #214 of The Weekly Challenge.
Last week we decided to give away FREE book coupon to Leo Manfredi but unfortunately we don&amp;rsquo;t have his email address. I request Leo please share your email to perlweeklychallenge@yahoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 212</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-212/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>