<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review #050</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-050/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-050/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Perl review for Week 050 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received the solution to &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 018&amp;rdquo; by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was a pleasant surprise to receive solution in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like C++, Go, Haskell, Javascript, Postscript, Prolog, R, Rust and HTML.
Please find below guest contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 052</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-052/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-052/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   A friend of mine, Jeff Goff (@DrForr) sadly killed in a scuba-diving accident while on vacation few days ago. I have known him for many years, mostly got to attend his talk at London Perl Workshop. I still remember his talk &amp;ldquo;The Art of Programming&amp;rdquo;. It was a very different experience where audience got to play with piece of paper during the entire talk. I only got the opportunity to have one-2-one conversation with him at The Perl Conference in Riga last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review #049</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-049/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-049/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Perl review for Week 049 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 051</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-051/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-051/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With last week contributions, I am currently placed at 46th position in the Top 50 contributors list. Andrezgz shared solutions to the Week #049 and Week #050 on top of last week challenge. Markus Holzer also shared solutions to the Week #019. Roger Bell_West shared blog for Week #047. Adam Russell shared the solutions to the last week challenge after a short break. Welcome back Adam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #051</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-051/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-051/</guid>
      <description>I am really enjoying the weekly challenges, specially doing in Raku. The point of blogging is also about sharing my fight with Raku. I hardly write anything about my Perl solution as I don&amp;rsquo;t see anything new to talk about. Having said that, I still go for Perl first as it is my first love and will remain so rest of my life. Even today, my brain is so tuned to Perl, every ideas come in form and shape of Perl only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 051</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-051/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-051/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   We are close to completing one year of weekly challenge. I am sure you would all agree, in this journey we have come across many experts in Perl and Raku. If you know of any Perl/Raku opportunities at your work place then please let us know about it. Similary if any member looking for any opportunities can reach out to us. We would then pass the contact details for you to take it further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #050</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-050/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-050/</guid>
      <description>I had great fun working with Merge Intervals task this week. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it was going to be more harder to solve than Noble number task. Keeping in mind the sample data provided with the task, I came up with solution very quickly. I was very happy with the result.
I then decided to share it on Twitter. Guess what happens next? The master of Unit Test, none other than E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 050</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-050/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-050/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With recent contributions, I finally made it to the Top 50 contributors list. Contributing in Raku is the main attraction for me. Did you notice that we now get regular contributions in other languages, specially Python, every week.
  GUESTS REPORT CARD   1) Ulrich Rieke: C++ (5), Haskell (6). 2) Orestis Zekai: Python (8). 3) Lubos Kolouch: Python (7). 4) User Person: Python (4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 050</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-050/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-050/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   It is time to announce our second winner of the year 2020. With great pleasure, we announce, Saif Ahmed, as winner of February 2020. Congratulations, Saif and thanks for your contributions, specially the tool EZPWC, created to help the Team PWC.
Every time new member joins the Team PWC, I get very excited. With time, I started to feel I know him/her so well. There is one more thing that excites me, is when I see an existing member coming back after the break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 049</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-049/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-049/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week, some Team PWC members contributing to the past challenges as well as the current week. It is always great to see the commitments by the members. Some of them listed below:
Yet Ebreo shared solutions to Perl Weekly Challenge - 036. Jaldhar H. Vyas shared the solutions with blog to Perl Weekly Challenge - 038. Roger Bell_West shared the blog for Perl Weekly Challenge - 046.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review #048</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-048/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-048/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Perl review for Week 048 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Raku Weekly Review #048</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-048/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-048/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Raku review for Week 048 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG: The Weekly Challenge #049</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-049/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/weekly-challenge-049/</guid>
      <description>This is my second blog for The Weekly Challenge. I am only able to participate, thanks to Ryan Thompson for helping me with the Perl and Raku reviews. I am going for Perl solutions first then will try to translate it into Raku next. I believe in coding to learn the language. With so many Raku experts around, I am not shy throwing questions up. I am now going to share my experience doing &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 049&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 049</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-049/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-049/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   We have seen rise of interest in the Perl Weekly Challenge recently and with that we have now 150 members in the Team PWC. We hope to keep you all engaged and interested. Please do share new ideas for challenges and any suggestion for improvement. We would like to thank Ruben Westerberg for suggesting task. We would also like to thank Herbert Bollermann (@HrBollermann) for interesting ideas for the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 048</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-048/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-048/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Today, I am going to talk about one of the prominent member of Team PWC, Arne Sommer. I am confident you must have come across his contributions. He has been taking in the weekly challenge for sometime now. He mostly does Raku solution. He also does blog every week. I would like to share a very special quality of him, i.e. creative blog title. Please checkout below what I mean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Raku Weekly Review: Challenge - #047</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-047/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Raku review for Week 047 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Updates 2020-Feb-24 › Arne Sommer sent me the source code for his Number::Roman library, which I&amp;rsquo;ve now reviewed.
2020-Feb-24 › Review added for Laurent Rosenfeld&amp;rsquo;s second solution. Sorry I missed it!
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - #047</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 01:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-047/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Perl review for Week 047 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first date with Raku</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/my-first-date-with-raku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/my-first-date-with-raku/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I started the Perl Weekly challenge i.e. 25th March 2019, I have been planning to take part in the weekly challenge. Because of lack of time, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t take part in the past. In the Week #046, I finally took the plunge and contributed Perl solutions to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 046.
Challenge #046 (Task #1) #!/usr/bin/perl use strict; use warnings; my @messages = ( &amp;#39;P + 2 l !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Raku Weekly Review: Challenge - #046</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-046/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-046/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Raku review for Week 046 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 048</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-048/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   In the Week #46, we introduced tool EZPWC, created by Saif Ahmed. Recently Saif released v0.06 with lots of features. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried it yet then please do give it a go and share your experience with us.
This week, there is a slight delay in Raku reviews by Ryan Thompson. Hopefully in the next few days, we would have it ready. Thanks for your patience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - #046</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-046/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-046/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Welcome to the Perl review for Week 046 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 047</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-047/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-047/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   We welcome Phillip Harris to the Team PWC and thanks for his first contributions in Perl.
Alicia Bielsa attempted to solve the Task #2 in Raku for the first time. Well done and hope to see more Raku solutions in coming week.
Jaldhar H. Vyas shared C++ solution to the Task #2 of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 044&amp;rdquo;.
Lubos Kolouch came back after a short break and not only shared solutions in Perl but also in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 047</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-047/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-047/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   We are pleased to announce that we have found Raku Reviewer to cover the temporary break by Laurent Rosenfeld. Any guess? He is the coolest kid in the team, Ryan Thompson. I would like to mention another gem from the team, Ulrich Rieke, who is a star contributor. He has been contributing regularly in Perl, Raku, C++ and Haskell.
You must have noticed there is a fixed set of members who blog about their solutions every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 046</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-046/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-046/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   As you must have noticed, we have a new player to review Perl and Raku solutions. No prize for any guess. He is none other than, Ryan Thompson, himself. I know it is NOT an easy task and that too doing both. Hats off to Ryan for accepting the challenge. Team members have already appreciated his quality reviews. Please do share your suggestions.
I also noticed familiar faces back in action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - #045</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-045/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-045/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Perl review for Week 045 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Continues from previous week.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!
We&amp;rsquo;d greatly appreciate any feedback you&amp;rsquo;d like to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Raku Weekly Review: Challenge - #045</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-045/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-045/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Raku review for Week 045 of the Weekly Challenge! For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
I&amp;rsquo;m filling in for Laurent this week with the Raku review.
Getting in Touch Email › Email me (Ryan) with any feedback about this review.
GitHub › Submit a pull request for any issues you may find with this page.
Twitter › Join the discussion on Twitter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 046</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-046/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-046/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Apology to all team members, the Weekly Challenge is still not on the track. Things have improved but there is still a lot to do. I am pleasantly suprised by the offer of help by all the team members. Ryan Thompson offered to do Perl Reviews, which is a big help. I will now have one less thing to worry about every week. Thanks Ryan Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 045</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-045/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-045/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   The biggest pleasnt surprise of last week, was by Arne Sommer. He has been religiously contributing quality Raku solutions with impeccable blog every week. For the first time last week, I noticed he contributed Perl solutions. In the past, I have seen Perl contributors started contributing Raku solutions but the reversal never happend before. This is the proudest moment for me. Thanks Arne Sommer for your continuous support and encouragement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 045</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-045/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-045/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week had been the toughest week for me. My dad is now back home and doing well. Thanks each and every person for the best wishes. I know everything is messed up at the moment. I came back from India with throat infection and really bad cough. I am not fully recovered yet but still improving day-by-day. I would like to thank Ryan Thompson for doing Perl Review in my absence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 044</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-044/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-044/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   The highlight of last week contribution was Prolog solution submitted by Darren Bottin. I missed few regular contributors of Python though. Please keep up the great work.
  CENTURION CLUB   Welcome Colin Crane to the Centurion Club. Ruben Westerberg moved up to rank #2. Scimon Proctor moved up to rank #11. Javier Luque moved up to rank #15. Ryan Thompson moved up to rank #16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - 044</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-044/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-044/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback. You can also contact me (Ryan) directly, with any feedback on this review.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Thompson › Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - 043</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-043/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-043/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback. You can also contact me (Ryan) directly, with any feedback on this review.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 042</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-042/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-042/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Octal Numbers This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 42 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to print decimal number 0 to 50 in Octal Number System.
For example:
Decimal 0 = Octal 0 Decimal 1 = Octal 1 Decimal 2 = Octal 2 [ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 044</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-044/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-044/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week was really upsetting for me, I had call from my brother (India) telling me that Dad is unwell and currently admitted in ICU. I made quick arrangement and flew to India last Friday. I met my Dad the next day at the hospital. It was an emotional re-union of Father &amp;amp; Son. I am planning to stay with him for a week and flying back coming Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - 042</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-042/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-042/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   Octal Number System Write a script to print decimal number 0 to 50 in Octal Number System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 043</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-043/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-043/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   One thing, I noticed recently is the quality of blogs by the members. I find it hard to give enough time to justify the quality content. I would like to thank each and every members for their support and encouragement.
  CENTURION CLUB   Welcome Burkhard Nickels to the Centurion Club. Ruben Westerberg moved up to rank #3. Scimon Proctor moved up to rank #11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 043</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-043/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-043/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   As you all know, **Perl Careers** has been the sole sponsor for the **Weekly Champion** through out the year 2019**, we are very grateful to Perl Careers** for the support. I have recently blogged (#1 and #2) with regard to attract more sponsors for the Weekly Champion. I will let you know as and when I hear any update in this regard.
In the year 2020, we decided to pick Monthly Champion, thanks to Perl Careers, once again for the support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 042</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-042/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-042/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week, few members came back after a short break, Jaldhar H. Vyas, Alicia Bielsa and Fabrizio Poggi, and shared solutions with us. We welcome all of them. We also had new member joining the team, Cristina Heredia from Madrid. We now have 141 members in the team.
Ryan Thompson recently offered to re-design the Challenges page. He has completed first round of layout changes. He is still working on pagination to make it easier to navigate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 041</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-041/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-041/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Attractive Numbers This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 41 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to display attractive number between 1 and 50.
A number is an attractive number if the number of its prime factors is also prime number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - 041</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-041/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-041/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   Write a script to display attractive number between 1 and 50.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 042</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-042/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-042/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Markus Holzer** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 041&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Markus, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Quick recap of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 041&amp;rdquo; by Mohammad S Anwar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Review: Challenge - 040</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-040/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   Show multiple arrays content You are given two or more arrays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: Rename Perl6 to Raku</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-raku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/welcome-raku/</guid>
      <description>I had been planning to kick start the mini project of renaming Perl6 to Raku on the official website of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;. And the side project to this, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be called &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp;amp; Raku&amp;rdquo;? This is sticky area and needed more time to go through various aspects. Renaming project wasn&amp;rsquo;t too difficult to deal with but I was looking for some FREE time to do it properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 041</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-041/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-041/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Kian-Meng Ang had been reviewing Perl Solutions since week #007. I know you all appreciated the quality review done by Kian-Meng Ang. For some reason, Kian-Meng decided to take a break from the voluntary job. I would like to take this opportunity to thank Kian-Meng Ang for all the hard work. The change in team forced me take over the role. So from now on, you would see weekly review of Perl Solutions by me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 040</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-040/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-040/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Multiple Arrays Content This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 40 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
You are given two or more arrays. Write a script to display values of each list at a given index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 040</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-040/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-040/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Colin Crain, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 039.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 040 winner Noud Aldenhoven. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Noud: Starting from a young age I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in Science and Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 039</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-039/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-039/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Data::Dumper, DateTime, DateTime::Duration, Function::Parameters, List::Util, Set::IntSpan, constant, feature, lib, strict, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 041</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-041/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-041/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Noud Aldenhoven** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 040&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Noud, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 040&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 040</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-040/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Merry Christmas &amp;amp; Happy New Year The last gift of Advent Calendar 2019 was presented by Jo Christian Oterhals. I would like to take this opportunity to thank each and every contributor to the Advent Calendar 2019.
Please checkout THANK YOU message.
Two new members, Duane Powell and Javier Luque, joined the Centurion Club last week. We now have 19 members in the club.
Burkhard Nickels shared Raku solutions for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 039</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-039/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-039/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Guest House This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 39 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
A guest house had a policy that the light remain ON as long as the at least one guest is in the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 - Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/merry-christmas-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/merry-christmas-2019/</guid>
      <description>Today December 25, 2019, we completed 9 months of weekly challenges. The Year 2019 will remain very special to all of us associated with &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;. We just celebrated Advent Calendar for the first time. It was fun revisiting some of the great contributions by fellow members.
I would like to take this opportunity to THANK our sole sponsor, Peter Sergeant of PerlCareers. We are looking for more sponsors in the Year 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-24/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Jo Christian Oterhals**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Niven Numbers** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 007&amp;rdquo;.
Print all the niven numbers from 0 to 50 inclusive, each on their own line. A niven number is a non-negative number that is divisible by the sum of its digits.  After a week’s hiatus I’ve returned to the Perl Weekly Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019/</guid>
      <description>With great pleasure, we announce our first Advent Calendar. Through out the festive season, you can expect interesting challenges with complete analytic solutions.      MON
 TUE WED THU FRI SAT SUN                    1            2
 3 4 5 6 7 8            9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Francis J Whittle**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Perfect Numbers** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 008&amp;rdquo;.
Write a script that computes the first five perfect numbers. A perfect number is an integer that is the sum of its positive proper divisors (all divisors except itself). Please check Wiki for more information. This challenge was proposed by Laurent Rosenfeld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 040</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-040/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Colin Crain** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 039&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Colin, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 039&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 039</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-039/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-039/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Advent Calendar 2019 is in the last leg. We have had some very interesting solutions by respected members of the team.
Day 1: Word Ladder Puzzle by Laurent Rosenfeld Day 2: Ranking by Dave Jacoby Day 3: Encode/Decode Roman Numerals by Joelle Maslak Day 4: Hoftadter Female and Male Sequence by E. Choroba Day 5: Longest english word using US state postal abbreviation by Neil Bowers Day 6: Pythagoras Pie Puzzle by Arne Sommer Day 7: Ackermann Function by Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-22/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by JJ Merelo**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Replace character and count** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 001&amp;rdquo;.
Write a script to replace the character ‘e’ with ‘E’ in the string ‘Perl Weekly Challenge’. Also print the number of times the character ‘e’ is found in the string.  I haven&amp;rsquo;t looked at the other solutions that have been published, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure they&amp;rsquo;ll go along these lines, at least in Raku.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 038</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-038/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-038/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Carp, Date::Calc, Date::Manip, DateTime, POSIX, Test::Exception, Test::More, Time::Local, Time::Piece, Try::Tiny, boolean, feature, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 037</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-037/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-037/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Daylight Loss or Gain This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 37 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to find out the Daylight gain/loss in the month of December 2019 as compared to November 2019 in the city of London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 038</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-038/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-038/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Date Finder This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 38 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script to accept a 7 digits number, where the first number can only be 1 or 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-21/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Gustavo Chaves**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Base35 Representation** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 002&amp;rdquo;.
Write a script that can convert numbers to and from a base35 representation, using the characters 0-9 and A-Y.  I cannot do it as a one-liner this time, but it was still fun. While trying to solve it I realized that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be much harder to implement a general solution to convert from any base to any base between 2 and 36.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Roger Bell_West. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Word Game** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 038&amp;rdquo;**.
Lets assume we have tiles as listed below, with an alphabet (A..Z) printed on them. Each tile has a value, e.g. A (1 point), B (4 points) etc. You are allowed to draw 7 tiles from the lot randomly. Then try to form a word using the 7 tiles with maximum points altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-19/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Khalid**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Strip leading zeros** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 002&amp;rdquo;.
Write a script or one-liner to remove leading zeros from positive numbers.  This solution uses Raku Grammer At first here is the code :
grammar Grammer { token TOP {&amp;lt;sign&amp;gt;? &amp;lt;int&amp;gt; &amp;lt;decimal&amp;gt;?} token decimal {&amp;lt;dot&amp;gt;&amp;lt;digit&amp;gt;?} token int {&amp;lt;zeros&amp;gt;? &amp;lt;digit&amp;gt;?} token digit { \d+ } token dot { &amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-18/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Philippe Bruhat**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: FizzBuzz** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 001&amp;rdquo;.
Write one-liner to solve FizzBuzz problem and print number 1-20. However, any number divisible by 3 should be replaced by the word fizz and any divisible by 5 by the word buzz. Numbers divisible by both become fizz buzz.  This one works by modifying the string until what’s we’re left with is the expected result:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-17/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Athanasius. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Bitcoin Validation** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 016&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to validate a given bitcoin address. Most Bitcoin addresses are 34 characters. They consist of random digits and uppercase and lowercase letters, with the exception that the uppercase letter “O”, uppercase letter “I”, lowercase letter “l”, and the number “0” are never used to prevent visual ambiguity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 038</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-038/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-038/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Javier Luque, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 037.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 038 winner Ryan Thompson. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Ryan: My interest in computing started as a hobby in the early ’80s, and got into MS-DOS freelance work around 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Yozen Hernandez. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Vigenère Cipher** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 015&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to implement Vigenère cipher. The script should be able encode and decode. Checkout wiki page for more information.  This seemed like a cool challenge to tackle. Knowing next to nothing about encryption, I was worried that this would take me all week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 037</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-037/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Data::Dumper, Date::Manip, DateTime, DateTime::Duration, DateTime::Event::Recurrence, Function::Parameters, List::Util, Modern::Perl, POSIX, Test::More, Time::Local, Time::Moment, Time::Piece, Time::Seconds, Time::localtime, constant, feature, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 039</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-039/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-039/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Ryan Thompson** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 038&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Ryan, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 038&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 038</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-038/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Advent Calendar 2019 is on full swing so far. We have had some very interesting solutions by respected members of the team.
Day 1: Word Ladder Puzzle by Laurent Rosenfeld Day 2: Ranking by Dave Jacoby Day 3: Encode/Decode Roman Numerals by Joelle Maslak Day 4: Hoftadter Female and Male Sequence by E. Choroba Day 5: Longest english word using US state postal abbreviation by Neil Bowers Day 6: Pythagoras Pie Puzzle by Arne Sommer Day 7: Ackermann Function by Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Javier Luque. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Dynamic Variable** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 031&amp;rdquo;**.
Create a script to demonstrate creating dynamic variable name, assign a value to the variable and finally print the variable. The variable name would be passed as command line argument.  This one is a bit more difficult, creating a dynamic variable in Perl wasn’t a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Scimon Proctor. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Pascal Triangle** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 003&amp;rdquo;**.
Create a script that generates Pascal Triangle. Accept number of rows from the command line. The Pascal Triangle should have at least 3 rows. For more information about Pascal Triangle, check this wikipedia page.  So Pascal&amp;rsquo;s Triangle is pretty and I decided I wanted to get it nicely laid out like so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-13/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Burkhard Nickels. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Demonstrate Array/Hash Slices** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 034&amp;rdquo;**.
 Demonstrate Array Slices or Hash slices.  \
To demonstate some different Array and Hash slicing features I do some image processing. An image is &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; that can be stored in 2- or 3-dimensional Arrays. To separate the data I will store the data in Hashes (Named Lists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Laurent Rosenfeld. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: nth Order Difference Series** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 023&amp;rdquo;**.
Create a script that prints nth order forward difference series. You should be a able to pass the list of numbers and order number as command line parameters. Let me show you with an example. Suppose we have list (X) of numbers: 5, 9, 2, 8, 1, 6 and we would like to create 1st order forward difference series (Y).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-11/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Yet Ebreo. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Sexy Primes** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 022&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to print first 10 Sexy Prime Pairs. Sexy primes are prime numbers that differ from each other by 6. For example, the numbers 5 and 11 are both sexy primes, because 11 - 5 = 6. The term “sexy prime” is a pun stemming from the Latin word for six: sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Mark Senn. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Split word on change of character** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 020&amp;rdquo;**.
 Write a script to accept a string from command line and split it on change of character. For example, if the string is “ABBCDEEF”, then it should split like “A”, “BB”, “C”, “D”, “EE”, “F”.  “There’s more than one way to do it” is a Perl programming motto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HELP: How to contribute?</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/how-to-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/how-to-contribute/</guid>
      <description>HELP: How to contribute?   Just submit Pull Request to GitHub repository with your solutions. First find out the latest challenge folder, more likely the highest numbered folder is the latest challenge folder e.g. challenge-002. If you are an existing member, you would probably find a folder by your name. For example, if your name is &amp;ldquo;Joe Blog&amp;rdquo; then there would be a folder called &amp;ldquo;joe-blog&amp;rdquo;. Under your named folder, you would find a file README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Dave Cross**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Find 5 Weekends** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 019&amp;rdquo;.
Write a script to display months from the year 1900 to 2019 where you find 5 weekends i.e. 5 Friday, 5 Saturday and 5 Sunday.  This would be simple enough to just brute-force. But when I started to think about it, I realised there’s a bit of a trick we can use which can cut down our search space quite significantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 037</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-037/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Duane Powell, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 036.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 037 winner Javier Luque. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Javier: I work for a company called Humanstate based in Sevenoaks and we run a platform called GivenGain that allows fundraisers to raise money for their favourite charities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 038</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-038/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Javier Luque** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 037&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Javier, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 037&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Adam Russell. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Priority Queue** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 018&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to implement Priority Queue. It is like regular queue except each element has a priority associated with it. In a priority queue, an element with high priority is served before an element with low priority. Please check this wiki page for more informations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 036</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-036/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-036/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Data::Validate::VIN, Function::Parameters, List::MoreUtils, List::Util, Readonly, Syntax::Construct, Test::Exception, Test::More, boolean, feature, strict, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 036</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-036/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-036/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Vehicle Identification Numbers (VIN) This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 36 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a program to validate given Vehicle Identification Number (VIN). For more information, please checkout wikipedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 037</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-037/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-037/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Advent Calendar 2019 is on full swing so far. We have had some very interesting solutions by respected members of the team.
Day 1: Word Ladder Puzzle by Laurent Rosenfeld Day 2: Ranking by Dave Jacoby Day 3: Encode/Decode Roman Numerals by Joelle Maslak Day 4: Hoftadter Female and Male Sequence by E. Choroba Day 5: Longest english word using US state postal abbreviation by Neil Bowers Day 6: Pythagoras Pie Puzzle by Arne Sommer Day 7: Ackermann Function by Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Jaldhar H. Vyas. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Ackermann Function** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 017&amp;rdquo;**.
Create a script to demonstrate Ackermann function as defined in wikipedia. 
As per the example in wiki page.
A(1, 2) = A(0, A(1, 1)) = A(0, A(0, A(1, 0))) = A(0, A(0, A(0, 1))) = A(0, A(0, 2)) = A(0, 3) = 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Arne Sommer. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #1: Pythagoras Pie Puzzle** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 016&amp;rdquo;**.
At a party a pie is to be shared by 100 guest. The first guest gets 1% of the pie, the second guest gets 2% of the remaining pie, the third gets 3% of the remaining pie, the fourth gets 4% and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Neil Bowers**. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Longest English word using US state postal abbreviation** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 014&amp;rdquo;.
Using only the official postal (2-letter) abbreviations for the 50 U.S. states, write a script to find the longest English word you can spell? Here is the list of U.S. states abbreviations as per wikipedia page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by E. Choroba. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Hofstadter Female and Male Sequences** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 013&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to demonstrate Mutually Recursive methods. Two methods are mutually recursive if the first method calls the second and the second calls first in turn. Using the mutually recursive methods, generate Hofstadter Female and Male sequences.  I used Function::Parameters to make the definition of the functions as close as possible to the ones given at Wikipedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Joelle Maslak. Today she is talking about her solutions to Task #1: Decimal to Roman** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 010&amp;rdquo;**.
Write a script to encode/decode Roman numerals. For example, given Roman numeral CCXLVI, it should return 246. Similarly, for decimal number 39, it should return XXXIX. Checkout wikipedia page for more informaiton.  To start with, I read the Wikipedia page referenced in the challenge, and realized there were several different systems for writing Roman numerals – it wasn’t as standardized as I thought!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Dave Jacoby. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Ranking in Perl** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 009&amp;rdquo;**.
1. Standard Ranking (1224): Items that compare equal receive the same ranking number, and then a gap is left in the ranking numbers. 2. Modified Ranking (1334): It is done by leaving the gaps in the ranking numbers before the sets of equal-ranking items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 036</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-036/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-036/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Steven Wilson, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 035.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 036 winner Duane Powell. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Duane: After getting a BS degree in Computer Science in 1985, I worked for a handful of defense contractors designing databases and writing programs in C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 037</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-037/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Duane Powell** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 036&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Duane, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 036&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2019-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2019
 The gift is presented by Laurent Rosenfeld. Today he is talking about his solutions to Task #2: Word Ladder** of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 007&amp;rdquo;**.
 Given two input words and a file that contains an ordered word list, implement a routine that finds the shortest ladder between the two input words. For example, for the words cold and warm, the routine might return: (&amp;ldquo;cold&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;cord&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;core&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;care&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;card&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;ward&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;warm&amp;rdquo;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 035</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-035/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-035/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Data::Dumper, Term::ANSIColor, Term::ANSIScreen, Term::Size::Perl, Test::More, Text::Morse, Text::Trim, Time::HiRes, autodie, constant, experimental, feature, lib, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 035</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-035/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-035/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Binary Encoded Morse Code This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 35 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The Challenge&amp;rsquo;s two tasks As usual, the challenge is made up of two tasks, but this time, the two tasks are so much inter-related that I&amp;rsquo;ll cover them together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 036</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-036/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-036/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   A gentle reminder to all members that we have launched Advent Calendar 2019 on 1st December 2019. Please do checkout. I hope you would enjoy the selected challenge every day. Please let us know what you think about it.
For the first time anyone submitted solutions in Haskell, all credit goes to our respected champion Ulrich Rieke. Also another champion Lubos Kolouch shared Python solutions. It gives me immense pleasure to receive solutions in guest languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 035</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-035/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-035/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Burkhard Nickels, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 034.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 035 winner Steven Wilson. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Steven: Around 10 years ago I was working in MIS in a local college and started to study Computing and Mathematics through the Open University which resulted in a degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 034</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-034/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-034/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge’s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Data::Dumper, Getopt::Long, List::Util, Modern::Perl, PDL, PDL::Core, PDL::IO::Image, PDL::ImageRGB, PDL::NiceSlice, feature, strict, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 034</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-034/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-034/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Array and Hash Slices This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 34 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge, contributed by Dave Cross, reads as follows:
Write a program that demonstrates using hash slices and/or array slices.
Slices are a way to access several values of an array or of a hash in one statement, by using multiple subscripts or keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 036</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-036/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-036/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Steven Wilson** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 035&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Steven, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
A gentle reminder to all members, please send us your nominated solutions for the Advent Calendar 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 035</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-035/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-035/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Today, Monday 25th Nov, 2019, we have completed 8 months of successfull run of The Weekly Challenge. Over the period, I came across many smart hackers. I have lots of personal favourites that I always look forward to their solutions. It always brings a big smile on my face every time I look at their solutions. Sometimes, I find it difficult to grasp in first reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 005</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-005/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Anagrams of a Word This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 5 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a program which prints out all anagrams for a given word. For more information about anagrams, please check this Wikipedia page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 034</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-034/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Ulrich Rieke, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 033.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 034 winner Burkhard Nickels. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Burkhard: Maybe I start with my private computer interests: Surely Perl; Linux, I installed Debian Linux on all my rather old computers; Now it is also Raspberry Pi; I did a little C/C++, HTML/CSS/Javascript; I wish to do a little with Computer Vision and Robotics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ Perl | Raku | The ] Weekly Challenge - 2020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/plan-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/plan-2020/</guid>
      <description>It has been wonderful journey so far in the year 2019. When I started the journey in March, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it would take this shape. All credit goes to the support of Perl/Raku community in general. It would be unfair if I pick few names. You know who I am talking about anyway. Let me share the story with you all.
I was working on 2 ideas at the start of the year 2019, &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;London Hack Day&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 033</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-033/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-033/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Data::Dumper, English, Getopt::Long, IO::All, List::Util, Modern::Perl, Mojo::File, feature, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 011</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-011/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #2: Displaying the Identity Matrix This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 11 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to create an Identity Matrix for the given size. For example, if the size is 4, then create Identity Matrix 4x4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 033</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-033/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-033/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Letter Count This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 33 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script that accepts one or more files specified on the command-line and count the number of times letters appeared in the files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 035</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-035/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-035/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Burkhard Nickels** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 034&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Burkhard, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
A gentle reminder to all members, please send us your nominated solutions for the Advent Calendar 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 034</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-034/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-034/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week Adam Russell** shared the solutions to &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;** in C++ as well. I think, it is the best way to refresh your knowledge by doing simple challenge. Also Steven Wilson, for the first time sent us solution in Raku. It makes me proud when I see cross language experiment. A big THANK YOU to all members.
For more information about &amp;ldquo;Guest Contributions&amp;rdquo;, please checkout blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 033</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-033/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Prajith P., the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 032.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 033 winner Ulrich Rieke. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Ulrich: There not so much a technical background. In fact, I do have a long-standing interest in rule-based syntactical systems and languages, starting from Latin at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 032</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-032/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-032/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
Additional feedback to the our Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account is much appreciated.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Data::Dumper, English, Getopt::Long, Getopt::Std, List::Util, Modern::Perl, Term::Size::Perl, Text::CSV_XS, feature, open, strict, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 004</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-004/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Computing the Digits of Pi This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 04 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to output the same number of PI digits as the size of your script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 032</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-032/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-032/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Word Histogram This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 32 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script that either reads standard input or one or more files specified on the command-line. Count the number of times and then print a summary, sorted by the count of each entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 034</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-034/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-034/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Ulrich Rieke** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 033&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Ulrich, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
I am working on the format of Perl Weekly Challenge Advent Calendar currently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 033</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-033/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-033/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Oretis Zekai started the tradition of solving the weekly challenge in a language different to others. For the first time, we received the solution in Python by Oretis Zekai in the week 18. Ever since respected team members took a keen interest as well and tried languages like C++, Postscript, Rust and HTML. We would like to say THANK YOU to each and every members for their contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 032</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-032/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-032/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Mark Senn, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 031.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 032 winner Prajith P.. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Prajith: Nothing much actually. I started Programming in Bash when I got my first job as a Linux server administrator at Ndimensionz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 031</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-031/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-031/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
  Task #1   CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, English, Modern::Perl, POSIX, Test::More, Try::Tiny, constant, experimental, feature, strict, utf8, warnings
Based on the submitted answers, there were three ways used by participants to solve this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 031</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-031/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-031/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Illegal Division by Zero This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 31 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a function to check divide by zero error without checking if the denominator is zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 033</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-033/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-033/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Prajith P.** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 032&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Prajith, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 032&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 032</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-032/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-032/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   &amp;ldquo;Hacktoberfest 2019&amp;rdquo; concluded recently, I am so proud of team members who actively participated and contributed towards the &amp;ldquo;Pull Request&amp;rdquo; count. At the end of the event, 41 team members submitted 185 Pull Requests as listed below:
 [&#39; 1: Yet Ebreo&#39;, 19], [&#39; 2: Joelle Maslak&#39;, 13], [&#39; 3: Lubos Kolouch&#39;, 13], [&#39; 4: E. Choroba&#39;, 10], [&#39; 5: Steven Wilson&#39;, 9], [&#39; 6: Dave Jacoby&#39;, 8], [&#39; 7: Roger Bell_West&#39;, 7], [&#39; 8: Andrezgz&#39;, 6], [&#39; 9: Dave Cross&#39;, 6], [&#39;10: Duane Powell&#39;, 6], [&#39;11: Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 031</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-031/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-031/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Kevin Colyer, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 030.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 031 winner Mark Senn. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Mark: Joined the U.S. Army as an attack helicopter crew chief to do what the Army described as &amp;ldquo;experimentation&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 030</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-030/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Date::Christmas, Date::Manip::Date, Date::Simple, DateTime, DateTime::Format::HTTP, Modern::Perl, POSIX, Test::More, Time::Local, Time::Piece, Time::Seconds, constant, feature, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Five-Smooth Numbers This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 03 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script to generate 5-smooth numbers, whose prime divisors are less or equal to 5. They are also called Hamming/Regular/Ugly numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 014</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-014/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Van Eck&amp;rsquo;s Sequence This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 14 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to generate Van Eck’s sequence starts with 0. For more information, please check out wikipedia page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 030</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-030/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Christmas on Sunday This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 30 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to list dates for Sunday Christmas between 2019 and 2100. For example, 25 Dec 2022 is Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 032</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-032/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-032/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Mark Senn** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 031&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Mark, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 031&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 031</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-031/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-031/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   It is Day 28 of &amp;ldquo;Hacktoberfest 2019&amp;rdquo;, I am so proud of team members actively participating and contributing towards the &amp;ldquo;Pull Request&amp;rdquo; count. As of now, 41 team members have submitted 162 Pull Requests as listed below:
 [&#39; 1: Yet Ebreo&#39;, 16], [&#39; 2: Lubos Kolouch&#39;, 13], [&#39; 3: Joelle Maslak&#39;, 12], [&#39; 4: E. Choroba&#39;, 9], [&#39; 5: Dave Jacoby&#39;, 7], [&#39; 6: Steven Wilson&#39;, 7], [&#39; 7: Roger Bell_West&#39;, 6], [&#39; 8: Andrezgz&#39;, 5], [&#39; 9: Duane Powell&#39;, 5], [&#39;10: Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damian Conway - Masterpiece Collection</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/damian-corner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/damian-corner/</guid>
      <description>Damian Conway wrote a blog in the last week of May 2019 and confessed that he has been quietly playing at home with &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;. With this started the regular blog by him picking weekly challenge and presenting his views.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to loose the track of all his great work, so I decided to put together all his blogs dealing with various challenges in one place. It would be a great read for anyone interested in the detailed analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 030</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-030/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-030/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Dave Jacoby, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 029.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 030 winner Kevin Colyer. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Kevin: This is an interesting question as I am a hobby programmer. I am a self-taught programmer starting as a teenager with an 8-bit Atari computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 031</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-031/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-031/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Kevin Colyer** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 030&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Kevin, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 030&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 030</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-030/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   It is Day 21 of &amp;ldquo;Hacktoberfest 2019&amp;rdquo;, I am so proud of team members actively participating and contributing towards the &amp;ldquo;Pull Request&amp;rdquo; count. As of now, 39 team members have submitted 124 Pull Requests as listed below:
 [&#39; 1: Yet Ebreo&#39;, 12], [&#39; 2: Joelle Maslak&#39;, 9], [&#39; 3: Lubos Kolouch&#39;, 9], [&#39; 4: Dave Jacoby&#39;, 6], [&#39; 5: E. Choroba&#39;, 6], [&#39; 6: Roger Bell_West&#39;, 6], [&#39; 7: Steven Wilson&#39;, 5], [&#39; 8: Andrezgz&#39;, 4], [&#39; 9: Daniel Mita&#39;, 4], [&#39;10: Duane Powell&#39;, 4], [&#39;11: Jaldhar H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 029</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-029/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-029/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Data::Dumper, Function::Parameters, Inline, JSON, List::Util, Modern::Perl, Parse::RecDescent, Test::Deep, Test::More, Text::Glob::Expand, feature, lib, strict, utf8, warnings
For a good write-up of the problem, read the explanation of the problem at Rosetta Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 029</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-029/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-029/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Expansion This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 29 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to demonstrate brace expansion. For example, script would take command line argument Perl {Daily,Weekly,Monthly,Yearly} Challenge and should expand it and print like below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 029</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-029/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-029/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Andrezgz, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 028.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 029 winner Dave Jacoby. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Dave: My first degree was in Journalism, but while I was told there was a language requirement for college, the school I attended had a computers requirement, which I did not meet, so I took a remedial course in BASIC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 030</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-030/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Dave Jacoby** as the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 029&amp;rdquo;**. Congratulations Dave, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 029&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 029</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-029/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-029/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   It is Day 14 of &amp;ldquo;Hacktoberfest 2019&amp;rdquo;, I am so proud of team members actively participating and contributing towards the &amp;ldquo;Pull Request&amp;rdquo; count. As of now, 27 team members have submitted 68 Pull Requests as listed below:
 [&#39; 1: Joelle Maslak&#39; , 8] [&#39; 2: Yet Ebreo&#39; , 8] [&#39; 3: Lubos Kolouch&#39; , 6] [&#39; 4: Dave Jacoby&#39; , 4] [&#39; 5: E. Choroba&#39; , 4] [&#39; 6: Roger Bell_West&#39; , 4] [&#39; 7: Steven Wilson&#39; , 3] [&#39; 8: Adam Russell&#39; , 2] [&#39; 9: Andrezgz&#39; , 2] [&#39;10: Daniel Mita&#39; , 2] [&#39;11: Dave Cross&#39; , 2] [&#39;12: Duane Powell&#39; , 2] [&#39;13: Duncan C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 028</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-028/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-028/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Cwd, File::Basename, File::MMagic, File::Type, Function::Parameters, Modern::Perl, Moose, Test::More, constant, feature, strict, utf8, warnings
We would recommend that you start with the solution by Duncan C White, Colin Crain and Joelle Maslak for their intriguing and well-written comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 006</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-006/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Compact Number Ranges This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 6 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script which takes a list of numbers from command line and print the same in the compact form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Niven (or Harshad) Numbers This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 7 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Print all the Niven numbers from 0 to 50 inclusive, each on their own line. A Niven number is a non-negative number that is divisible by the sum of its digits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 028</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-028/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-028/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: File Types This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 28 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to check the file content without explicitly reading the content. It should accept file name with path as command line argument and print “The file content is binary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 015</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-015/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Vigenère Cipher This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 15 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to implement Vigenère cipher. The script should be able encode and decode. Checkout wiki page for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 016</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-016/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: The Largest Share in the Pythagoras Pie This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 22 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
At a party a pie is to be shared by 100 guests. The first guest gets 1% of the pie, the second guest gets 2% of the remaining pie, the third gets 3% of the remaining pie, the fourth gets 4% and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 017</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-017/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Parsing URLs With a Perl 6 Grammar This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 17 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Create a script to parse URL and print the components of URL. According to Wiki page, the URL syntax is as below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-018/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Longest Common Substrings This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 18 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script that takes 2 or more strings as command line parameters and print the longest common substring. For example, the longest common substring of the strings “ABABC”, “BABCA” and “ABCBA” is string “ABC” of length 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-019/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Five Weekends in a Month This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 19 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to display months from the year 1900 to 2019 where you find 5 weekends i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-020/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Split Strings on Character Change This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 20 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to accept a string from command line and split it on change of character. For example, if the string is &amp;ldquo;ABBCDEEF&amp;rdquo;, then it should split like &amp;ldquo;A&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;BB&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;D&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;EE&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;F&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 021</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-021/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Euler&amp;rsquo;s Number This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 21 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to calculate the value of e, also known as Euler’s number and Napier’s constant. Please checkout this wiki page for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 022</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-022/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Sexy Prime Pairs This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 22 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to print first 10 Sexy Prime Pairs. Sexy primes are prime numbers that differ from each other by 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 027</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-027/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-027/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Intersection of Two Straight Lines This is derived in part from my blog post made in answer to the Week 27 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script to find the intersection of two straight lines. The co-ordinates of the two lines should be provided as command line parameter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 028</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-028/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-028/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Scimon Proctor, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 027.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 028 winner Andrezgz. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Andrezgz: I&amp;rsquo;ve been close to computers since I was 8. My first programming experience came with Basic, then Logo (yeah, with the turtle) and then branched out to dBase, DOS networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 029</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-029/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-029/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Andrezgz as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 028. Congratulations Andrezgz, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week Perl Weekly Challenge - 028.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 028</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-028/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-028/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Dave Jacoby has been an inspirational and never missed an opportunity to impress me with his exceptional knowledge of not just Perl. This time, he used good old friend html to tackle the Task #2: Digital Clock. Please do checkout his work in action.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 027</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-027/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-027/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Function::Parameters, Getopt::Long, List::Util, Modern::Perl, Moose, Regexp::Common, Test::Exception, Test::More, feature, strict, utf8, warnings
Start with the submission by Duncan C White.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 027</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-027/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-027/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Roger Bell_West, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 026.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 027 winner Scimon Proctor. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Scimon: I&amp;rsquo;ve been in love with computers since seeing Visicalc do magic stuff with numbers sometime in the 70&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 028</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-028/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-028/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Scimon Procotor as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 027. Congratulations Scimon, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
As you all know Hacktoberfest is starting from tomorrow, I wrote an introduction blog sharing few tips how to succeed in the challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 027</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-027/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-027/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   The Hacktoberfest fever is already gone viral. I am convinced you must have heard of the contest by now. If you are Perl Weekly Challenge regulars then you need not worry as doing just the weekly challenge in the month of October is enough to cross the line.
I have written a blog with suggestions/tips.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 026</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-026/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Getopt::Long, List::Util, Test::More, feature, strict, warnings
As with past challenges, simple task will lead to diverse solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 026</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-026/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Yet Ebreo, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 025.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 026 winner Roger Bell_West. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Roger: I was a hobbyist in the early 1980s (along with what seemed like everyone else in the UK in the wake of the BBC Micro), and it gradually developed into something people would pay me for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 027</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-027/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-027/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Roger Bell West as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 026. Congratulations Roger, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 026</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-026/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With every week, we are adding new member to the Centurion Club. We are so proud of each and every members of the team. At the end of week 26, we now have 114 active members. Please do spread the word among your friends and colleagues. Let us make this a global event together.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 025</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-025/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Graph, List::MoreUtils, List::Util, Memoize, Modern::Perl, Parallel::WorkUnit, Storable, constant, feature, strict, utf8, warnings
Out of curiosity, of all submitted solutions, which participant have the fastest implementation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 025</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-025/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Lubos Kolouch, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 024.
Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 025 winner Yet Ebreo. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Yet Ebreo: I started programming when I was 12. My first ever code was written in mIRC scripting language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 026</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-026/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Yet Ebreo as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 025. Congratulations Yet Ebreo, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 025</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-025/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week, I noticed proactive interaction among team members while solving Task #1 of Perl Weekly Challenge - 025. Do you want to see yourself, checkout yourself the comments section to the blog by Laurent Rosenfeld. There was an issue raised by Laurent Rosenfeld. I liked the innovative way to reach out to fellow team member.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 024</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-024/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: B, strict, warnings
Read the excellent blog post by Arne Sommer on his investigation to find the shortest solution in both Perl 5 and Perl 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 024</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-024/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Athanasius, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 023. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 024 winner Lubos Kolouch. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Lubos: I started coding when I was 10 - at that time using a smart calculator :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 025</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-025/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Lubos Kolouch as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 024. Congratulations Lubos, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 024</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-024/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   At the end of week 24, we now have 10 members in the Centurion Club. They are the consistent players of the club. I noticed one thing about the list, except Scimon Proctor, all others have been the weekly champion.
  Laurent Rosenfeld (286)
  Joelle Maslak (258)
  Jaldhar H. Vyas (212)
  Ruben Westerberg (180)
  Adam Russell (156)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 023</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-023/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Carp, Const::Fast, Function::Parameters, Getopt::Long, Getopt::Std, List::Util, Modern::Perl, Regexp::Common, Test::Exception, Test::More, autodie, constant, experimental, feature, strict, utf8, warnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 023</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-023/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Kian-Meng Ang, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 022. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 023 winner Athanasius. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Athanasius: Learned some programming at school, first on an HP-65 calculator and then using Fortran IV on punch cards!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 024</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-024/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Athanasius as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 023. Congratulations Athanasius, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 023</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-023/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Arne Sommer, joined the Perl Weekly Challenge in the second week. Ever since, he has been contributing solutions in Perl6 along with great blog every week without break. Last week, he surprised me by submitting solutions to the first week challenge that he missed out earlier. He submitted solutions in Perl5, Perl6 with blog. I hope it inspires other to do take similar challenge and enlighten us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 022</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-022/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: Const::Fast, Function::Parameters, LWP::UserAgent, List::Util, Math::Primality, Math::Prime::Util, Memoize, Modern::Perl, autodie, boolean, constant, feature, lib, strict, utf8, warnings
We have yet another question related to prime number, therefore most participants will reuse back their solution from previous challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 022</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Ruben Westerberg, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 021. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 022 winner Kian-Meng Ang. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Kian-Meng: Nothing fancy, just a regular LAMP stack web developer. You probably can get more details from my personal blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 023</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-023/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   With great pleasure, we announce Kian-Meng Ang as the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 022. Congratulations Kian-Meng, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
  RECAP   Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 022</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-022/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week, Yet Ebreo, joined the Perl Weekly Challenge like any other team members. However I noticed something special about him. He appeared to be very enthusiasts. In the very first week, He submitted solutions in Perl5 and Perl6. Well he didn&amp;rsquo;t stop there, he even blogged about it. Did he stop there? Well not, he started solving all the past challenges. In the series, he started with Perl Weekly Challenge - 001, [P5 #1], [P5 #2], [P6 #1] and [P6 #2].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 021</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-021/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  CPAN modules used: bignum, Carp, Const::Fast, Getopt::Long, Math::AnyNum, Math::Big, Math::BigFloat, Math::Big, Math::BigRat, Math::NumberCruncher, Math::Symbolic, Modern::Perl, Sidef, Test::More and Text::Table::Tiny.
The biggest takeaway for this task was the solution by Randy Lauen where he did a comparison of different CPAN modules against the formulated calculation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 021</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Duncan C. White, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 020. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 021 winner Ruben Westerberg. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Ruben: I am a design engineer/systems engineer developing sensor systems and DGRT (http://dgrt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 022</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-022/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 021 and the name is Ruben Westerberg. Many congratulations Ruben, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 021</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-021/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   The highlight of last week is the start of new weekly series of Perl6 Review of weekly challenges by Laurent Rosenfeld. With the launch blog we now have [Task #1] and [Task #2]. Please do share your views and suggestions to better serve the purpose.
Please accept my apology for not being able to share my views on the solutions received. I promise to get that right in the next week edition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-020/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to review thing a bit differently for this week by listing down all the CPAN modules used for a particular task. The modules usage reflects three things, the coding style of a participant (Function::Parameters) the common used module (Math::Prime::Util) to solve a particular problem, and the trend of module usage (Modern::Perl) which was seen quite often in the last few challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-020/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Arne Sommer, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 019. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 020 winner Duncan C. White. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Duncan: I&amp;rsquo;ve been programming since about 1976, using BASIC on various micro computers (RML 380Z in school, Apple II, Sinclair ZX80/81/Spectrum, Oric Atmos, BBC micro, Atari ST etc), then graduating to Unix machines in 1983 at University while doing a Computer Science degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 021</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-021/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 020 and the name is Duncan C. White. Many congratulations Duncan, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-020/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Apology for late releasing without any comments. Last week I was too busy with The Perl Conference in Riga. Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.
  DAMIAN&amp;rsquo;s CORNER   Watch this space for Damian&amp;rsquo;s blog about Perl Weekly Challenge. Damian picked up the Wrap paragraph task of Perl Weekly Challenge - 019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-019/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
This week challenge was quite straight forward and they said, simpler tasks will always leads to more creative solutions.
 Task #1  In general, this was quite a straight forward question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-019/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to E. Choroba, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 018. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 019 winner Arne Sommer. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Arne: I started programming in about 1982, when I bought an Atari 400 computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 020</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-020/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 019 and the name is Arne Sommer. Many congratulations Arne, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-019/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   The main attraction of last week challenge was Dave Cross. Why? Because it managed to brought Dave Cross back in action. He didn&amp;rsquo;t just stop there but he even blogged about it. We noticed some of the active members being busy getting ready for next week Perl Conference in Riga. We would like to thank each members for taking time out in the busy schedule and participarted in the weekly challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-018/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Yozen Hernandez, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 017. Today we are talking to the Perl Weekly Challenge - 018 winner E. Choroba. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Choroba: Both my parents were mathematicians. Despite the iron curtain (I&amp;rsquo;m from the Czech Republic) and technological embargo of the Eastern block in the 80&amp;rsquo;s, my father was able to get a Commodore computer for me, so I started with Basic and Assembler at the age of 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-018/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  If you need to have a quick overview how to solve the challenge, read the submitted solutions by Mark Anderson, Jamie, and E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 019</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-019/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 018 and the name is E. Choroba. Many congratulations Choroba, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-018/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Last week, we had a guest contributor, Orestis Zekai, works as a Software Engineer. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Perl but fluent in Python. He came across earlier weekly challenges and found it fun. So he decided to solve the Perl Weekly Challenge - 018 using Python language, Task #1 and Task #2. He wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be part of weekly competition, though.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 017</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-017/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, go through the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  For a good overview on how this recursive formulae works, you can look at this animated calculator.
This seemed like a straight forward question, a direct translation and implementation of the Ackermann function using the definition of the formulae given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 017</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-017/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Adam Russell, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 016. Today we are talking to the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 017&amp;rdquo; winner Yozen Hernandez. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Yozen: I have a BA in Computer Science from Hunter College, CUNY, and a PhD in Bioinformatics from Boston University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-018/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 017 and the name is Yozen Hernandez. Many congratulations Yozen, you should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 017</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-017/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   When I proposed Bhagavad Git API task for the Perl Weekly Challenge - 017, I was hoping one of team member from India would pick this up. Our API task leader, Joelle Maslak, has been beaten by Randy Lauen, who just joined the team. As usual, Joelle always takes up API task in Perl5 and Perl6. This time, Adam Russell also joined the group for API task this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 016</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-016/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. We highly appreciate and welcome your feedback.
For a quick overview, read the original tasks and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  The Pythagoras Pie Puzzle, which was originally published in the Pythagoras Magazine and made known through the Guardian&amp;rsquo;s article.
While this is a simple question, we loved how Duncan C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 016</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-016/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Joelle Maslak, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 015. Today we are talking to the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 016&amp;rdquo; winner Adam Russell. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Adam: I am presently a Principal Software Engineer for Optum, which is part of United Health Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - Optional API Task</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/the-optional-api-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/the-optional-api-task/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking to do review of optional API task so far. I have now finally got the time.
  BACKGROUND   During the Perl Weekly challenge 005, Gabor Szabo, Chief Editor of Perl Weekly newsletter proposed optional API task to the weekly challenge. He even suggested list of API that I could use every week. It took me couple of weeks to figure out the format and other formalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 017</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-017/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 016 and the name is Adam Russell. Many congratulations to Adam. You should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 016</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-016/</guid>
      <description>HEADLINES   I would like to share this blog by Damian Conway where he shared his view with regard to the &amp;ldquo;Strong/Weak prime numbers&amp;rdquo; task of Perl Weekly Challenge - 015. You must have noticed Neil Bowers love for the optional API task. Last week DetectLanguage API task was another example where he created CPAN distribution WebService::DetectLanguage for the API task. It is now even listed as official Perl Client on their website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 015</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-015/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. Feedback are very much appreciated and welcome.
For a quick overview, read the original questions and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Task #1  Since this question is related to Perl Weekly Challenge #12, quite a few participants (Adam Russell, Jaldhar H. Vyas, Yozen Hernandez, E. Choroba, and others) were using and adapting their answer from Perl Weekly Challenge #12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 015</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-015/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Jaldhar H. Vyas, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 014. Today we are talking to the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 015&amp;rdquo; winner Joelle Maslak. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Joelle: I started programming, in BASIC on an Apple II compatible computer, when I was a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 016</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-016/</guid>
      <description>Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 015 and the name is Joelle Maslak. Many congratulations to Joelle. You should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 015</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-015/</guid>
      <description>Let me welcome, Veesh Goldman, after a short break. He is the first member of the team. It is always nice to see member coming back after short break.
Last but not the least, keep contributing to the weekly challenge, making sure we keep the focus on Fun and Knowledge Sharing.
 Adam Russell Adam surprised me with the use of prime url. Clean separation of method to filter strong and weak prime numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 014</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-014/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
Last week we spoke to Laurent Rosenfeld, the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 013. Today we are talking to the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge - 014&amp;rdquo; winner Jaldhar H. Vyas. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Jaldhar: I was first introduced to computers in England (where I was born) by the Sinclair ZX Spectrum, a 1MZ 8-bit computer with a massive 48K of RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: Perl Weekly Challenge - 013</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-013/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the weekly series &amp;ldquo;Meet The Champion&amp;rdquo;.
In the weekly series, we would talk to the winner of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; and find out more about him/her. In this first blog of the series, we are talking to our first champion Laurent Rosenfeld. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
  Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Laurent: I graduated as a software engineer in 1996 (at age 40) and I have been working in this capacity (mainly development) ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 014</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-014/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous post.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. Feedback are very much appreciated and welcome. For a quick overview, read the original questions and recap of the weekly challenge.
 Challenge #1  Some participants found that it&amp;rsquo;s quite vogue to understand the Van Eck&amp;rsquo;s sequence but managed to understand it through OEIS and Numberphile&amp;rsquo;s video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 015</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-015/</guid>
      <description>Let me announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 014 and the name is Jaldhar H. Vyas. Many congratulations to Jaldhar. You should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 014</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-014/</guid>
      <description>Last week, Dave Jacoby sent us the first solution in Perl5 as Pull Request [#294]. Then came a new member, 95th member, **Robert Van Dam&amp;rdquo;. Being a first timer, it didn&amp;rsquo;t stop him in taking API challenge either.
We have had maximum number of new members joining last week. We now have 100 active members in the team. By the time, you are reading this, we have already declared our second winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 013</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-013/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous post.
Feel free to submit a merge request or open a ticket if you found any issues with this post. Feedback are very much appreciated and welcome.
Read the original questions and recap of the weekly challenge first to have a quick overview.
 Challenge #1  In this challenge, there are three approaches to generate all the last Fridays for a year. We can either (1) count forward from first Friday of the year, (2) count backward from last Friday of the year, or (3) count backward from the last day of each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - Story so far ...</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/the-story-of-pwc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/the-story-of-pwc/</guid>
      <description>We are now 3 months old and growing fast every week with the support of wider Perl Community.
The prime motto of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; is to promote Perl (be it Perl5 or Perl6). I was looking for fun way of doing it. Being, co-editor of Perl Weekly newsletter, I noticed that not many people blog about interesting use of the language. I must say, Perl6 community is doing far better than Perl5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 014</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-014/</guid>
      <description>Without any further delay, we would like to announce the winner of Perl Weekly Challenge - 013 and the name is Laurent Rosenfeld. Many congratulations to Laurent. You should soon hear from Perl Careers about your reward. Please do let us know how you feel about it. For rest of the participants, I would say Good Luck for next time. Keep sending in your solutions and share your knowledge with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 013</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-013/</guid>
      <description>This week, Joelle Maslak sent us the first solution in Perl6 as Pull Request [#265]. Then came Scimon Proctor, again in Perl6 as Pull Request [#266]. Kevin Colyer submitted the next in Perl6 as Github gist. By now, I started thinking where are all #Perl5 hackers. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to wait longer, Pete Houston sent us the solution in Perl5 by email. Finally we had our first complete solution in Perl5 by Dave Jacoby as Pull Request [#271].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 012</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-012/</guid>
      <description>Continues from last week.
For a quick overview, read through all questions and recap of the challenge first.
This week was quite unique as we observed there were several submissions where submissions were based on existing solutions but were done in a more alternative and elegant way. Moreover, some of these show case the expressiveness of Perl programming language itself, which is also one of the key goal of this weekly challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 013</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-013/</guid>
      <description>Couple of weeks ago, I tweet below about a surprise for all registered members.
It is now time to annouce the surprise. Few weeks ago, Peter Sergeant of PerlCareers contacted me by email and offered to sponsor the weekly challenge to make it more attractive. He offered the winner of weekly challenge $50 Amazon Voucher. We, Peter and I, worked out the formalities and other related issues. All registered members who contribute to the weekly challenge for the week will go into the ballot box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 012</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-012/</guid>
      <description>I was little late in releasing the weekly challenge last time. If I remember correctly it was around 4am Monday morning. Still, by 9am (UK time), I had first solution as PR by none other than the Scimon Procotor himself. And within the next hour, he submitted the solution to the second challenge. By lunch time, I had one more member Ozzy submitted solution to the first challenge.
This week, Joelle Maslak joined 100+ score club and became the second member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 011</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-011/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
For a quick overview, read through all questions and recap of the challenge first.
For those who are new to the weekly review post, the main purpose of weekly review is to document down interesting approaches of using Perl programming language to solve each week challenges. Code reading or review allows us to learn / relearn, discover / rediscover, and appreciate / reappreciate (some participants uses other programming languages in their day job) new, interesting, and quirky things accomplished with Perl (unfortunately Perl 5 for now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 012</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-012/</guid>
      <description>With every week, the team is growing and participation is also growing. I also love the fact that members even taking on optional API challenge regularly now. I hope, you are having fun solving weekly challenges as much as I am.
 RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.
 CHART Please take a look at the charts showing interesting data.
I would like to thank everyone for their valuable suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 011</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-011/</guid>
      <description>I noticed members taking on the optional API challenge more regularly. Before only handfull members bother taking the challenge. I am also happy to see familiar faces coming back to the weekly challenge after short break. I hope they continue with it and enlighten us.
 Adam Russell Adam solved the Fahrenheit-Celcius challenge in such a way that even a kid would follow it without any explanation. Simply Cool. He treated the second challenge of Identity Matrix in the similar fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 010</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-010/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous week.
For a quick overview, read through the questions and recap of the challenge.
 Challenge #1  The Wikipage page have a good introduction and manual calculation of conversion of Arabic numerals to Roman numerals. Read Laurent Rosenfeld&amp;rsquo;s blog post for the finer implementation details.
Most participants uses a hash to map between Arabic and Roman numerals. Since order of the matching roman numerals against the Arabic values is important, we&amp;rsquo;ll need to sort it before any conversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 011</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-011/</guid>
      <description>I noticed regular flow of new members to the team of Perl Weekly Challenge. Some of them quite actively take part in the challenge as well as blog about it. Some while on vacation, didn&amp;rsquo;t miss to take on weekly challenge. I remember, one member, submit the solution from her sickbed. I am gratefull to each of them for their support. I am equally thankfull to those who take time and blog about their solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 010</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-010/</guid>
      <description>I noticed few members came back after a short break. Welcome back. It is always nice to see you taking part in the weekly challenge. I hope to see you again and again. I would like to this opportunity to welcome new members. I hope you are having fun with the challenges. The moto of the weekly challenge is to have fun solving the challenges and learn from others. It feels nice when I hear positive feedbacks from the members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous post. Follow up on this week review of Perl Weekly Challenge #009 answers submitted by all the participants. Read the full question list and the recap of the challenge to have an overview before we proceed with our review.
 Challenge #1  Since most first question is beginner friendly, there are two steps to solve the problem. First, we need to loop through a series of numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 010</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-010/</guid>
      <description>I came to know about one secret player of Perl Weekly Challenge just few days ago. Any guesses? He is the Damian Conway. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t need any introduction. My first encounter with him was when I bought his book Perl Best Practices. I have been a big fan of him since then. Checkout his blog. I would also like to mention another newly joined member Yozen Hernandez. He blogged first time ever that too about his solution to the Perl Weekly Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>I would like to this opportunity to thank one of the respected member Kian-Meng Ang for the help in reviewing Perl 5 challenges every week. Checkout her last review if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen already. Ever since I started reviewing the challenges, I am looking for volunteer to do the same for Perl 6. I know it is weekly commitment and can be tiresome. If we can create team of reviewers for each languages then it would be even more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>Follow up on this week review of the Perl Weekly Challenge #008 of answers submitted by all the participants. Read the full question list and the recap of the challenge to have an overview before we proceed with our review.
 Challenge #1  Looking through all the submissions, there are several approaches used by these participants to calculate the first five perfect numbers which are 6, 28, 496, 8128, and 33550336.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>The best part of Perl Weekly Challenge is that you are free to take a break for as long as you want. Even then you are encourged to take a look at others solution and enjoy. I personally recommend you should read the blog by the elite members. They are invaluable source of knowledge. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Enjoy the challenge.
 RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge - 008 participation was same as the Challenge - 007 in terms of number of members participated. However this time we received more than solution with the introduction of the optional third API challenge. As a matter of fact, Joelle Maslak care to answer the third challenge. She solved the third challenge in Perl5 and Perl6.
 Adam Russell Adam making good use of unpack() to solve the perfect numbers challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Review: Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Below is the write-up review (only covers Perl 5) of the Perl Weekly Challenge #007 of all the submitted answers. You can read the original questions first to understand the details of these two challenges.
 Challenge #1  If we read the question carefully, there are several steps to solve this problem. First, to find all niven number from 0 to 50 inclusively. Second, to find the sum of its digits of this range of number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge has been very innovative with so many unique solutions. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Keep the momentum up. Good luck with this week challenge, I am sure you will find it fun and enjoyable.
 RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.
 CHART Please take a look at the charts showing interesting data.
I would like to thank everyone for your valuable suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Last week was better than the previous week. I noticed big rush on Saturday and Sunday always. As we are getting into 8th week, members are getting the hang of it, which is nice.
 Adam Russell Adam once again came up with unique solution using pack and unpack to solve the challenge #1. I really liked the graph solution for challenge #2. [#1] [#2] [BLOG]
Alicia Bielsa Alicia submitted the solution to the challenge #1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge has been very innovative with so many unique solutions. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Keep the momentum up. Good luck with this week challenge, I am sure you will find it fun and enjoyable.
 RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.
 CHART Please take a look at the charts showing interesting data.
I would like to thank everyone for your valuable suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 006</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-006/</guid>
      <description>Last week was not very active in terms of number of participations. Having said that the quality of the solutions is always on the top. Some went for the kill, you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to miss it. Enjoy the code.
 Adam Russell Adam got the help from CPAN module Data::Dump and the end result is unbelievable simple. Check out his code.
Alicia Bielsa Alicia submitted the solution to the first question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 006</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-006/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge introduced me to so many genious around the globe. It would be unfair to name a few. You know who I am talking about. The main objective of the project was to introduce Perl to more people and allow sharing the magic of Perl. In the last 5 weeks, I can say that I have personally learnt a lot from many greats.
 RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 005</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-005/</guid>
      <description>I would like to talk about blog written by some members this week. In the past, I went into the details of Perl 5 solutions mainly. Lets change the trend this time.
Following blogs have been reported last week. Each blog is a text book in itself as it teaches you so many things. I enjoyed reading each and every blog. Please do read them when you get time.
 Adam Russell https://adamcrussell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 005</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-005/</guid>
      <description>The best part of the Perl Weekly Challenge is reading the blog by the members. Personally, I like the journey of an idea to final solution. If you look at closely all the blogs, every member has unique style. They all think differently but ends up with the same result. I have become fan of few in the last few weeks. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, reading code is fascinating but boring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 004</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-004/</guid>
      <description>For the first time ever, I published RECAP blog before the weekly challenge. It is the sign that things are settling down. Members are using Pull Request more frequently to submit the solutions. Last Sunday, when I made the Challenge 004 public, I couple of people responded in no time.
The first person was Kivanc Yazan and he announced it on Twitter.
The next person followed him was @smokemachine. He has been regular since last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 004</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-004/</guid>
      <description>I noticed last week, less participation than the previous week. Why? Honestly speaking I have no clue. Could it be the questions were too tricky for the challenge? The week before, I received the feedback that the questions were too easy and simple. So I went for little trickier one this time. It seems that I have to balance it somehow.
I am gratefull to all members submitting the solutions as Pull Request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Every week, I release the challenge by email first and then on Twitter. I wait for about 30 minutes to get the first response to the challenge. I also look at the Google Analytics Realtime Chart to see how many users are reading the new challenge page and from which part of the world.
Last week, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to wait long, I saw the first reaction on Twitter from Khalid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Solution for Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>As received in response to the challenge by Philippe Bruhat. Highly recommended.
 Write a script or one-liner to remove leading zeros from positive numbers.
 As a filter:
perl -ple &#39;s/^0+//&#39;  Challenge #2  Write a script that can convert numbers to and from a base35 representation, using the characters 0-9 and A-Y.
 Those who remember The Perl Review Code golf contest may remember this challenge.
In February 2002, brian d foy wanted to try his hand at publishing a Perl magazine (following the demise of The Perl Journal).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>I noticed the timing of releasing the weekly challenge is not helping anyone in UK timezone as I released around mid-night. So if somebody who lives in other side where it is day they get to try the challenge first. I realised within few hours of making the challenge public, I starts getting feedback but none from UK member. It is only when it is Monday morning, I see reactions from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Last week challenge turned out to be a cakewalk for Perl 6 hackers. This shows my lack of knowledge of Perl 6. I have requested our inhouse Perl 6 experts to share some challenging questions. I already received few and kept in the challenge bank. I will use it in the coming weeks. Credit will be given to the hacker when published. We highly recommend that you submit you solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first weekly recap of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;.
Apology for the delay, I was supposed to release this blog with the second challenge of the series. I promise next blog is going to be on time.
For the first time ever, the Monday 25th March 2019, was not depressing like any other Monday. Thanks to &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;, I was so busy following public reactions on Twitter. It was a memorable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>It is already time for the second challenge of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. We have had very positive response so far. We will soon share the review of first challenge. You can send us your solutions by replying the same email that drops the weekly challenge to your inbox. If you are active on twitter then you can DM @PerlWChallenge as well. Or if you have GitHub profile then you can even submit your solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Solution for Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>This is actually as we received in response to the challenge by Philippe Bruhat. Highly recommended.
Challenge #1 Write a script to replace the character ‘e’ with ‘E’ in the string ‘Perl Weekly Challenge’. Also print the number of times the character ‘e’ found in the string.
 $ perl -E &#39;$_=shift;say y/e/E/;say&#39; &#39;Perl Weekly Challenge&#39; 5 PErl WEEkly ChallEngE Historical note: y///c is called &amp;ldquo;Abigail&amp;rsquo;s length horror&amp;rdquo; by golfers and obfuscators (couldn&amp;rsquo;t trace where the term came from).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Week a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first task of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. Every Monday, we are going to propose 2 challenges, one aimed at Beginners and another for Experts. However you are free to choose the challenge you fancy. You can even attempt to solve both. As you know the choice of languages are Perl and Raku. You can solve one challenge in Perl and other in Raku, if you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Week a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first task of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. Every Monday, we are going to propose 2 challenges, one aimed at Beginners and another for Experts. However you are free to choose the challenge you fancy. You can even attempt to solve both. As you know the choice of languages are Perl and Raku. You can solve one challenge in Perl and other in Raku, if you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Perfect Numbers This is derived from my blog post made in answer to the Week 8 of the Perl Weekly Challenge organized by Mohammad S. Anwar as well as answers made by others to the same challenge.
The challenge reads as follows:
Write a script that computes the first five perfect numbers. A perfect number is an integer that is the sum of its positive proper divisors (all divisors except itself).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Rosenfeld Weekly Review: Challenge - 018</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-000/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/p6-review-challenge-000/</guid>
      <description> Raku Solutions Weekly Review  Task #1: Split Strings on Character Change </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/readme/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>