<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perl5 on Perl Weekly Challenge - Perl5 &amp; Perl6</title>
    <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perl5 on Perl Weekly Challenge - Perl5 &amp; Perl6</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://perlweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>Continues from previous post. Follow up on this week review of Perl Weekly Challenge #009 answers submitted by all the participants. Read the full question list and the recap of the challenge to have an overview before we proceed with our review.
Challenge #1 Since most first question is beginner friendly, there are two steps to solve the problem. First, we need to loop through a series of numbers. Next, determine whether a square number has at least five distinct digits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 010</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-010/</guid>
      <description>I came to know about one secret player of Perl Weekly Challenge just few days ago. Any guesses? He is the Damian Conway. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t need any introduction. My first encounter with him was when I bought his book Perl Best Practices. I have been a big fan of him since then. Checkout his blog. I would also like to mention another newly joined member Yozen Hernandez. He blogged first time ever that too about his solution to the Perl Weekly Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>I would like to this opportunity to thank one of the respected member Kian-Meng Ang for the help in reviewing Perl 5 challenges every week. Checkout her last review if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen already. Ever since I started reviewing the challenges, I am looking for volunteer to do the same for Perl 6. I know it is weekly commitment and can be tiresome. If we can create team of reviewers for each languages then it would be even more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kian-Meng Ang Weekly Review: Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>Follow up on this week review of the Perl Weekly Challenge #008 of answers submitted by all the participants. Read the full question list and the recap of the challenge to have an overview before we proceed with our review.
Challenge #1 Looking through all the submissions, there are several approaches used by these participants to calculate the first five perfect numbers which are 6, 28, 496, 8128, and 33550336.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 009</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-009/</guid>
      <description>The best part of Perl Weekly Challenge is that you are free to take a break for as long as you want. Even then you are encourged to take a look at others solution and enjoy. I personally recommend you should read the blog by the elite members. They are invaluable source of knowledge. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Enjoy the challenge.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge - 008 participation was same as the Challenge - 007 in terms of number of members participated. However this time we received more than solution with the introduction of the optional third API challenge. As a matter of fact, Joelle Maslak care to answer the third challenge. She solved the third challenge in Perl5 and Perl6.
Adam Russell Adam making good use of unpack() to solve the perfect numbers challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Review: Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/review-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Below is the write-up review (only covers Perl 5) of the Perl Weekly Challenge #007 of all the submitted answers. You can read the original questions first to understand the details of these two challenges.
Challenge #1 If we read the question carefully, there are several steps to solve this problem. First, to find all niven number from 0 to 50 inclusively. Second, to find the sum of its digits of this range of number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 008</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-008/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge has been very innovative with so many unique solutions. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Keep the momentum up. Good luck with this week challenge, I am sure you will find it fun and enjoyable.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.
CHART Please take a look at the charts showing interesting data.
I would like to thank everyone for your valuable suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Last week was better than the previous week. I noticed big rush on Saturday and Sunday always. As we are getting into 8th week, members are getting the hang of it, which is nice.
Adam Russell Adam once again came up with unique solution using pack and unpack to solve the challenge #1. I really liked the graph solution for challenge #2. [#1] [#2] [BLOG]
Alicia Bielsa Alicia submitted the solution to the challenge #1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 007</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-007/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge has been very innovative with so many unique solutions. Thanks to all the members for participating and blogging about it. Keep the momentum up. Good luck with this week challenge, I am sure you will find it fun and enjoyable.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.
CHART Please take a look at the charts showing interesting data.
I would like to thank everyone for your valuable suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 006</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-006/</guid>
      <description>Last week was not very active in terms of number of participations. Having said that the quality of the solutions is always on the top. Some went for the kill, you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to miss it. Enjoy the code.
Adam Russell Adam got the help from CPAN module Data::Dump and the end result is unbelievable simple. Check out his code.
Alicia Bielsa Alicia submitted the solution to the first question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 006</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-006/</guid>
      <description>Perl Weekly Challenge introduced me to so many genious around the globe. It would be unfair to name a few. You know who I am talking about. The main objective of the project was to introduce Perl to more people and allow sharing the magic of Perl. In the last 5 weeks, I can say that I have personally learnt a lot from many greats.
RECAP Here is the recap of last week challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 005</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-005/</guid>
      <description>I would like to talk about blog written by some members this week. In the past, I went into the details of Perl 5 solutions mainly. Lets change the trend this time.
Following blogs have been reported last week. Each blog is a text book in itself as it teaches you so many things. I enjoyed reading each and every blog. Please do read them when you get time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 005</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-005/</guid>
      <description>The best part of the Perl Weekly Challenge is reading the blog by the members. Personally, I like the journey of an idea to final solution. If you look at closely all the blogs, every member has unique style. They all think differently but ends up with the same result. I have become fan of few in the last few weeks. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, reading code is fascinating but boring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 004</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-004/</guid>
      <description>For the first time ever, I published RECAP blog before the weekly challenge. It is the sign that things are settling down. Members are using Pull Request more frequently to submit the solutions. Last Sunday, when I made the Challenge 004 public, I couple of people responded in no time.
The first person was Kivanc Yazan and he announced it on Twitter.
The next person followed him was @smokemachine. He has been regular since last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 004</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-004/</guid>
      <description>I noticed last week, less participation than the previous week. Why? Honestly speaking I have no clue. Could it be the questions were too tricky for the challenge? The week before, I received the feedback that the questions were too easy and simple. So I went for little trickier one this time. It seems that I have to balance it somehow.
I am gratefull to all members submitting the solutions as Pull Request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Every week, I release the challenge by email first and then on Twitter. I wait for about 30 minutes to get the first response to the challenge. I also look at the Google Analytics Realtime Chart to see how many users are reading the new challenge page and from which part of the world.
Last week, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to wait long, I saw the first reaction on Twitter from Khalid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Solution for Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>As received in response to the challenge by Philippe Bruhat. Highly recommended.
 Write a script or one-liner to remove leading zeros from positive numbers.
 As a filter:
perl -ple &#39;s/^0+//&#39;  Challenge #2  Write a script that can convert numbers to and from a base35 representation, using the characters 0-9 and A-Y.
 Those who remember The Perl Review Code golf contest may remember this challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>I noticed the timing of releasing the weekly challenge is not helping anyone in UK timezone as I released around mid-night. So if somebody who lives in other side where it is day they get to try the challenge first. I realised within few hours of making the challenge public, I starts getting feedback but none from UK member. It is only when it is Monday morning, I see reactions from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Last week challenge turned out to be a cakewalk for Perl 6 hackers. This shows my lack of knowledge of Perl 6. I have requested our inhouse Perl 6 experts to share some challenging questions. I already received few and kept in the challenge bank. I will use it in the coming weeks. Credit will be given to the hacker when published. We highly recommend that you submit you solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first weekly recap of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;.
Apology for the delay, I was supposed to release this blog with the second challenge of the series. I promise next blog is going to be on time.
For the first time ever, the Monday 25th March 2019, was not depressing like any other Monday. Thanks to &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;, I was so busy following public reactions on Twitter. It was a memorable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>It is already time for the second challenge of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. We have had very positive response so far. We will soon share the review of first challenge. You can send us your solutions by replying the same email that drops the weekly challenge to your inbox. If you are active on twitter then you can DM @PerlWChallenge as well. Or if you have GitHub profile then you can even submit your solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Solution for Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>This is actually as we received in response to the challenge by Philippe Bruhat. Highly recommended.
Challenge #1 Write a script to replace the character ‘e’ with ‘E’ in the string ‘Perl Weekly Challenge’. Also print the number of times the character ‘e’ found in the string.
 $ perl -E &#39;$_=shift;say y/e/E/;say&#39; &#39;Perl Weekly Challenge&#39; 5 PErl WEEkly ChallEngE  Historical note: y///c is called &amp;ldquo;Abigail&amp;rsquo;s length horror&amp;rdquo; by golfers and obfuscators (couldn&amp;rsquo;t trace where the term came from).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Week a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first task of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. Every Monday, we are going to propose 2 challenges, one aimed at Beginners and another for Experts. However you are free to choose the challenge you fancy. You can even attempt to solve both. As you know the choice of languages are Perl5 and Perl6. You can solve one challenge in Perl5 and other in Perl6, if you like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>