<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perl on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perl on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 10, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 9 | Day 10 |  The gift is presented by Stephen G Lynn. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 217. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Challenge 1 (Sorted Matrix)  We are given a n by n matrix of numbers, and asked to report the third-smallest number in the matrix.
The specification seems to allow arbitrary non-numeric elements too, but since all the test examples are numeric, I will restrict to numeric matrices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 |  Welcome to our 5th Advent Calendar. We have had enormous amount of blog post shared by Team PWC members. In this edition of Advent Calendar, we are going to pick some of the best creative work by the expert members of Team PWC.                         MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: August 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-08/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about BarrOff Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we declared Mariano Spadaccini, the winner of July 2023.
Today we are talking to BarrOff, the winner of August 2023 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
BarrOff: After graduating school I studied chemistry but towards the end of my bachelors it became obvious that I want to do something computer science related.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Champion: November 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/meet-the-champion-2023-11/</guid>
      <description>Get to know about Peter Meszaros Welcome to the monthly series Meet The Champion.
Last month we declared Packy Anderson, the winner of October 2023.
Today we are talking to Peter Meszaros, the winner of November 2023 of The Weekly Challenge. I hope you are going to enjoy the interview.
 Mohammad: Tell us about your technical background?
Peter: I received my MSc.E.E. at BME Budapest in 1987 then I worked for Hungarian power system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 9, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 8 | Day 9 | Day 10 |  The gift is presented by Robbie Hatley. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 215. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1: Odd one Out  &amp;quot;You are given a list of words (alphabetic characters only) of same size. Write a script to remove all words not sorted alphabetically and print the number of words in the list that are not alphabetically sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 8, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 7 | Day 8 | Day 9 |  The gift is presented by Flavio Poletti. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 214. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 The challenge  You are given a list of numbers. You will perform a series of removal operations. For each operation, you remove from the list N (one or more) equal and consecutive numbers, and add to your score N × N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 7, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 6 | Day 7 | Day 8 |  The gift is presented by Matthias Muth. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 213. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1: Fun Sort  You are given a list of positive integers. Write a script to sort the all even integers first then all odds in ascending order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 6, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 5 | Day 6 | Day 7 |  The gift is presented by Peter Campbell Smith. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 212. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Lead to Gold and 1 2 3 Task - Jumping letters  You are given a word having alphabetic characters only, and a list of positive integers of the same length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 5, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 4 | Day 5 | Day 6 |  The gift is presented by Avery Adams. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 210. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Perl Weekly Challenge #210  I&amp;rsquo;m back this week with PWC #210. Last week I was very busy and spent a long time reviewing other peoples&amp;rsquo; far more efficient solutions to #208, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to doing any solutions for #209.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 4, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 3 | Day 4 | Day 5 |  The gift is presented by Dave Jacoby. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 209. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Give A Little Bit  Welcome to Weekly Challenge #209. I can’t do another HTTP.cats pic because 209 is not an assigned HTTP response code, but it is the area code for a huge part of central California, including Calaveras county, made famous by Mark Twain and The Celebrated Jumping Frog of Calaveras County.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>