<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perl on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perl on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/perl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 21, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-21/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 20 | Day 21 |  The gift is presented by Yves Orton. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 237. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Seize The Day - Simple Rules The Day  My solution was based on using Time::Local to compute the epoch for noon on the first day of the month, and then stepping forward by day until the required day of week has been found, and then stepping forward by week until the required repetition of that day has been found, or we ran off the end of the calender month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 |  Welcome to our 5th Advent Calendar. We have had enormous amount of blog post shared by Team PWC members. In this edition of Advent Calendar, we are going to pick some of the best creative work by the expert members of Team PWC.                         MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 20, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 19 | Day 20 | Day 21 |  The gift is presented by Jaldhar H. Vyas. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 235. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Challenge 1: Remove One  You are given an array of integers. Write a script to find out if removing ONLY one integer makes it strictly increasing order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 19, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-19/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 18 | Day 19 | Day 20 |  The gift is presented by Packy Anderson. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 234. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Common, but Unequal, Triplet Characters  Ok, trying to be creative with my title for this week’s Perl Weekly Challenge 334 blog title is probably a miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 18, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 17 | Day 18 | Day 19 |  The gift is presented by Lubos Kolouch. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 233. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1 - Similar Words  Introduction Programming often presents challenges that may seem trivial at first glance, but when delved into, bring out intriguing nuances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 247</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-247/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-247/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 248</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-248/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-248/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Shortest Distance 10. TASK #2: Submatrix Sum HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #248 of The Weekly Challenge.
Happy Holiday season to Team PWC members. I would like to take this opportunity to thank each member for the support and encouragement. With new year just couple of weeks behind, let us all enjoy the holiday break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 15, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 14 | Day 15 | Day 16 |  The gift is presented by Adam Russell. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 225. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Sentenced To Compute Differences  The examples used here are from the weekly challenge problem statement and demonstrate the working solution.
Part 1 You are given a list of sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 14, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 13 | Day 14 | Day 15 |  The gift is presented by Roger Bell_West. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 223. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Counting Boxes  Task 1: Count Primes You are given a positive integer, $n. Write a script to find the total count of primes less than or equal to the given integer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 12, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 11 | Day 12 | Day 13 |  The gift is presented by Simon Green. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 220. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Common Squares  Weekly Challenge 220 This is the second consecutive week I&amp;rsquo;ve done the task and written the blog 40,000+ feet in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>