<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, Gleam, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LocalStack with AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI.  1. Introduction 2. Setup awscli 3. Setup LocalStack 4. Make Bucket 5. List Buckets 6. Upload File 7. Download File 8. Delete File 9. List Bucket 10. Remove Bucket 11. S3 with Python 12. S3 with Perl 13. What next? Introduction  Recently I got the opportunity to work with AWS S3 at work.
For this I wanted to brush up my knowledge as last I played with it was an year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 23, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 22 | Day 23 | Day 24 |  The gift is presented by Luca Ferrari. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 298. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Perl Weekly Challenge 298  This post presents my solutions to the Perl Weekly Challenge 298.
I keep doing the Perl Weekly Challenge in order to mantain my coding skills in good shape, as well as in order to learn new things, with particular regard to Raku, a language that I love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 22, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-22/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 21 | Day 22 | Day 23 |  The gift is presented by Packy Anderson. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 286. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Spammer Game  For some reason, my brain saw “Order Game” and I thought “Circle Game“. Perhaps because my wife and I watched a Joni Mitchell documentary last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 16, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 15 | Day 16 | Day 17 |  The gift is presented by Ryan Thompson. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 276. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Maximum Frequency and now my Day is Complete  This post is part of a series on Mohammad Anwar’s excellent Weekly Challenge, where hackers submit solutions in Perl, Raku, or any other language, to two different challenges every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 11, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-11/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 10 | Day 11 | Day 12 |  The gift is presented by Simon Green. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 261. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Weekly Challenge 261  Task #1: Element Digit Sum  You are given an array of integers, @ints. Write a script to evaluate the absolute difference between element and digit sum of the given arra  My solution  Given that Perl doesn&amp;rsquo;t care (most of the time) between numbers and strings, this is one of those challenges that is easier to do in Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 23, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 22 | Day 23 | Day 24 |  The gift is presented by Ian Rifkin. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 240. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 A.A.B.A. (Acronym And Build Array)  Task 1: Acronym You are given an array of strings and a check string. Write a script to find out if the check string is the acronym of the words in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 19, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-19/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 18 | Day 19 | Day 20 |  The gift is presented by Packy Anderson. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 234. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Common, but Unequal, Triplet Characters  Ok, trying to be creative with my title for this week’s Perl Weekly Challenge 334 blog title is probably a miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 18, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-18/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 17 | Day 18 | Day 19 |  The gift is presented by Lubos Kolouch. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 233. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Task 1 - Similar Words  Introduction Programming often presents challenges that may seem trivial at first glance, but when delved into, bring out intriguing nuances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 12, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 11 | Day 12 | Day 13 |  The gift is presented by Simon Green. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 220. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Common Squares  Weekly Challenge 220 This is the second consecutive week I&amp;rsquo;ve done the task and written the blog 40,000+ feet in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>