<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, CUDA, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, Gleam, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 17, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-17/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 16 | Day 17 | Day 18 |  The gift is presented by Walt Mankowski. Today he is talking about his solutioni to The Weekly Challenge - 326. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Day of the Year and Decompressed List I did this week&amp;rsquo;s challenges in Perl and Python. A combination of language features and modules allowed me to solve them in just a few lines of code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 15, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 14 | Day 15 | Day 16 |  The gift is presented by Packy Anderson. Today he is talking about his solutioni to The Weekly Challenge - 319. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 This week in the Perl Weekly Challenge, I’m free associating. I want to use a Bag for task 2, and my wife has a bag from her production of Ragtime two and a half years ago that whenever she uses it, I sing 🎶 The people called it Bag-time… 🎶</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 13, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-13/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 12 | Day 13 | Day 14 |  The gift is presented by Simon Green. Today he is talking about his solutioni to The Weekly Challenge - 316. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Weekly Challenge: Sub circular Each week Mohammad S. Anwar sends out The Weekly Challenge, a chance for all of us to come up with solutions to two weekly tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grafana &#43; Prometheus</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/grafana-prometheus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/grafana-prometheus/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. What is Grafana? 2. What is Prometheus? 3. Docker Setup 4. Test Environment 5. Datasource 6. Dashboard What is Grafana?  Grafana is an open-source analytics and visualisation platform. It lets you create dashboards that visualise data from various sources such as:
- Prometheus (metrics and monitoring) - InfluxDB (time-series data) - Elasticsearch - PostgreSQL / MySQL etc.  It’s very popular for monitoring servers, containers, applications especially when paired with Prometheus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS S3 Bucket Events</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-bucket-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-bucket-events/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Setup Environment 3. Using aws 4. Using Python 5. Using Perl Introduction  Recently I shared my experience with Amazon S3 and Amazon Lambda.
Today I am playing with S3 Bucket Events and how it can be triggered and captured.
In this post, I will take a closer look at the following events.
- s3:ObjectCreated:Put - s3:ObjectCreated:Copy - s3:ObjectRemoved:Delete - s3:ObjectCreated:Post - s3:ObjectCreated:CompleteMultipartUpload Setup Environment  As with all other AWS related experiments, I want LocalStack running in a docker container.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Setup LocalStack 3. Lambda Function 4. Using aws 5. Using Python 6. Using Perl Introduction  This post comes nearly a month and a half after the last one. The previous post on an AWS related topic was about AWS DynamoDB. The break wasn&amp;rsquo;t intentional, though.
AWS Lambda is a serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to manage servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Customer Key Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Customer Provided Keys (SSE-C) 3. Using aws 4. Using Python 5. Using Perl Introduction  Continuing the blog series on AWS encryption, this post focuses on Server-Side Encryption using Customer-Provided Keys.
Previously, I covered the other two types of Server-Side Encryption i.e. S3 Encryption and KMS Encryption.
In this type of encryption, customer generates and manages the encryption key.
AWS does not store customer keys, they must be provided with every API request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Bedrock</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-bedrock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-bedrock/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. What&amp;rsquo;s Ollama? 3. Install Ollama 4. Run Ollama 5. FastAPI 6. Mock Bedrock - Python 7. Mock Bedrock - Perl 8. Uvicorn 9. Mock Test Introduction  Recently I was introduced to AWS Bedrock at work. Ever since, I&amp;rsquo;ve had many questions around it.
In this post, I am sharing my first encounter.
AWS Bedrock is a fully managed service offered by Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS KMS Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS KMS Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Using aws 3. Using Python 4. Using Perl Introduction  This post is in continuation of the last post where we explored the AWS S3 Encryption.
In this post, I would like to talk about encryption using AWS Key Management Service.
AWS Key Management Service (KMS) is a managed service that enables easy encryption of data using cryptographic keys.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>