<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JavaScript on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JavaScript on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, Gleam, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 14, 2023</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2023-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2023 | Day 13 | Day 14 | Day 15 |  The gift is presented by Roger Bell_West. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 223. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2023 from the original post.
 Counting Boxes  Task 1: Count Primes You are given a positive integer, $n. Write a script to find the total count of primes less than or equal to the given integer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 20, 2022</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2022-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2022-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2022 | Day 19 | Day 20 | Day 21 |  The gift is presented by Roger Bell_West. Today he is talking about his solution to &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 192&amp;rdquo;. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2022 from the original post by him.
 Equal Flips For All I’ve been doing the Weekly Challenges.
The latest involved a binary negation and list division. (Note that this is open until 27 November 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>