<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>localstack on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/localstack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in localstack on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/localstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS S3 Bucket Trigger</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-bucket-trigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-bucket-trigger/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Setup Environment 3. Using aws 4. Using Python 5. Using Perl Introduction  Recently I shared my experience with Amazon S3 and Amazon Lambda.
Today I am playing with S3 Bucket Events and how it can be triggered and captured.
In this post, I will take a closer look at the following events.
s3:ObjectCreated:Put s3:ObjectCreated:Copy s3:ObjectCreated:Post s3:ObjectCreated:CompleteMultipartUpload s3:ObjectRemoved:Delete Setup Environment  As with all other AWS related experiments, I want LocalStack running in a docker container.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Setup LocalStack 3. Lambda Function 4. Using aws 5. Using Python 6. Using Perl Introduction  This post comes nearly a month and a half after the last one. The previous post on an AWS related topic was about AWS DynamoDB. The break wasn&amp;rsquo;t intentional, though.
AWS Lambda is a serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to manage servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Customer Key Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Customer Provided Keys (SSE-C) 3. Using aws 4. Using Python 5. Using Perl Introduction  Continuing the blog series on AWS encryption, this post focuses on Server-Side Encryption using Customer-Provided Keys.
Previously, I covered the other two types of Server-Side Encryption i.e. S3 Encryption and KMS Encryption.
In this type of encryption, customer generates and manages the encryption key.
AWS does not store customer keys, they must be provided with every API request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS KMS Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS KMS Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Using aws 3. Using Python 4. Using Perl Introduction  This post is in continuation of the last post where we explored the AWS S3 Encryption.
In this post, I would like to talk about encryption using AWS Key Management Service.
AWS Key Management Service (KMS) is a managed service that enables easy encryption of data using cryptographic keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS S3 Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS S3 Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Types of S3 Encryption 3. Server-Side Encryption (SSE) 4. Client-Side Encryption (CSE) 5. AWS Managed Keys (SSE-S3) 6. Using aws 7. Using Python 8. Using Perl Introduction  A week ago, I wrote a blog post about AWS S3 using the LocalStack platform. It was originally intended to cover just the basic operations. However, a few days later, I updated the post to include object versioning in AWS S3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LocalStack with AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI.  1. Introduction 2. Setup awscli 3. Setup LocalStack 4. Make Bucket 5. List Buckets 6. Upload File 7. Download File 8. Delete File 9. List Bucket 10. Remove Bucket 11. S3 with Python 12. S3 with Perl 13. What next? Introduction  Recently I got the opportunity to work with AWS S3 at work.
For this I wanted to brush up my knowledge as last I played with it was an year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>