<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-cloudfront/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-cloudfront/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. 1. Introduction 2. What&amp;rsquo;s AWS CloudFront? 3. Setup Origin 4. Create Content 5. Setup Configuration 6. Create Distribution 7. Mock CloudFront 8. Testing Time 9. Cleanup Introduction  Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re running a FastFood shop and you want to deliver food as fast as possible to customers all over the world.
But if your shop is only in, say, London, someone in Paris might have to wait a long time for their food to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 325</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-325/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-325/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 326</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-326/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-326/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Day of the Year 10. TASK #2: Decompressed List HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #326 of The Weekly Challenge.
Thank you, HVukman, for introducing a new programming language, PicoLisp. and sharing solution to Task #2.
Thank you, Team PWC, for your support and contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, Gleam, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Customer Key Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-customer-key-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. Customer Provided Keys (SSE-C) 3. Using aws 4. Using Python 5. Using Perl Introduction  Continuing the blog series on AWS encryption, this post focuses on Server-Side Encryption using Customer-Provided Keys.
Previously, I covered the other two types of Server-Side Encryption i.e. S3 Encryption and KMS Encryption.
In this type of encryption, customer generates and manages the encryption key.
AWS does not store customer keys, they must be provided with every API request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 324</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-324/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-324/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Bedrock</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-bedrock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-bedrock/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using ChatGPT. 1. Introduction 2. What&amp;rsquo;s Ollama? 3. Install Ollama 4. Run Ollama 5. FastAPI 6. Mock Bedrock - Python 7. Mock Bedrock - Perl 8. Uvicorn 9. Mock Test Introduction  Recently I was introduced to AWS Bedrock at work. Ever since, I&amp;rsquo;ve had many questions around it.
In this post, I am sharing my first encounter.
AWS Bedrock is a fully managed service offered by Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS KMS Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS KMS Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Using aws 3. Using Python 4. Using Perl Introduction  This post is in continuation of the last post where we explored the AWS S3 Encryption.
In this post, I would like to talk about encryption using AWS Key Management Service.
AWS Key Management Service (KMS) is a managed service that enables easy encryption of data using cryptographic keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 325</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-325/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-325/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Consecutive One 10. TASK #2: Final Price HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #325 of The Weekly Challenge.
Thank you, Yitzchak Scott-Thoennes, for sharing the blog post for the first time.
Thank you, HVukman, for sharing solution in J.
I noticed a big dip in guest contributions as compared to a week before i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 323</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-323/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-323/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>