<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map::Tube Unicode</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/map-tube-unicode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/map-tube-unicode/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Just a few days ago, I shared an experimental feature added to the Map::Tube, routing framework. It involved adding metadata to stations. You can find out more about it in this post.
In the same spirit, here&amp;rsquo;s one more fature that has been introduced: support for Unicode characters in station names.
To give you some context, when I originally wrote this framework, it was primarily for the London Tube Map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 317</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-317/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-317/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 318</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-318/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-318/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Group Position 10. TASK #2: Reverse Equals HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #318 of The Weekly Challenge.
Today is the Monday Bank Holiday in England. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be rest day unlike usual start of the week activities.
I hope and wish you had great Easter break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map::Tube experimental</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/map-tube-experimental/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/map-tube-experimental/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Map::Tube is one of my earliest creations. It was made public on 25th October 2010 to be precise.
I&amp;rsquo;ve given talks on the topic at various Perl conferences and even contributed an article to the Perl Advent Calendar 2024.
There&amp;rsquo;s also a 5-part blog series initiated by Pual Cochrane on the subject. You can check out part one and I highly recommend following the rest of the series as it gets published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 316</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-316/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 317</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-317/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-317/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Acronyms 10. TASK #2: Friendly Strings HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #317 of The Weekly Challenge.
This week turned out to be a welcome back week.
I&amp;rsquo;m super happy to see so many team members back to the fold and shared their story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/cve-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/cve-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  1. What&amp;rsquo;s CVE? 2. Key Features 3. How CVE works? 4. Why CVE matters? 5. How to audit? 6. Why recreate CVEs? 7. Known CVEs 8. Recreate CVEs 9. Further Sources  What&amp;rsquo;s CVE?  CVE stands for Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures.
It is a publicly available dictionary of known cybersecurity vulnerabilities and exposures.
It provides a standardised way to identify and track security issues in software and hardware systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 315</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-315/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-315/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 316</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-316/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. SPONSOR 3. RECAP 4. PERL REVIEW 5. RAKU REVIEW 6. CHART 7. NEW MEMBERS 8. GUESTS 9. TASK #1: Circular 10. TASK #2: Subsequence HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #316 of The Weekly Challenge.
Today is the first Monday of the month and it&amp;rsquo;s time to declare the next champion!
With great pride, I announce, Eric Cheung, as the Champion of the Month for March 2025.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>