<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientist in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/scientist-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/scientist-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Scientist in Perl  It was in the year 2017, I found out about the CPAN module Scientist and guess what?
It turned out be created by a very dear friend of mine, Lance Wicks.
I submitted few pull requests, mostly low hanging fruits, during that period and it was kindly accepted and merged.
You might ask me, what is Scientist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Extraction in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/extraction-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/extraction-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Text Extraction in Perl  I have always been fascinated about image processing but never got my head around it.
Even today, I barely know anything about it.
Text extraction from image is something, I always wanted to try but never managed to do it successfully.
I tried first in Perl but when I failed in my attempt then I tried in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/future-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/future-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Future in Perl  Recently I have been playing with Concurrent and Parallel Programming in Perl.
It is something that I don&amp;rsquo;t get to do on daily basis.
Having said this exercise, gave me an opportunity to try key features and document for future reference.
In the series, today I am talking about Futures in my favourite programming language Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 311</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-311/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 312</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-312/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Minimum Time 10. TASK #2: Balls and Boxes HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #312 of The Weekly Challenge.
I wish all members who celebrate the month of Ramadan. May ALLAH s.w.t. bless you with peace, happiness and prosperity.
I would also like to congratulate all fellow Indians for Team India winning the Champions Trophy 2025 for the second time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 310</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-310/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCE - How to?</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/mce-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/mce-how-to/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  MCE, Many-Core Engine provides parallel processing capabilities in Perl.
It is now one of my favourite CPAN module when it comes to parallel processing.
There is another player, Parallel::ForkManager, if you are interested.
Having said, MCE is designed primarily for process-based parallelism, and NOT thread-based parallelism.
MCE uses processes to isolate the execution of each task, allowing each process to operate independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 311</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-311/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-311/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Upper Lower 10. TASK #2: Group Digit Sum HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #311 of The Weekly Challenge.
Today is the first Monday of the Month and time to declare the next champion.
With great pride, I announce Peter Campbell Smith the next champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slurp in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/slurp-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/slurp-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  We all know, in Perl v5.36, a new command line flag -g was introduced. For more information you can checkout PPC-0011.
The new flag sets $/ (input record separator) to undef and therefore enables slurp mode.
It&amp;rsquo;s simply an alias for -0777.
Those who are old enough, might remember this -0777 magical number.
So what is -0777?
As per the official documentation:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>