<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 313</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-313/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 314</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-314/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Equal Strings 10. TASK #2: Sort Column HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #314 of The Weekly Challenge.
We have a new member, Darren Yates, joining Team PWC.
Welcome aboard! I hope you find our group fun and entertaining while also surprising you with its magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform with Docker</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.       Terraform with Docker  1. Introduction 2. Objectives 3. What is Terraform? 4. Why Terraform? 5. Terraform Configuration File 6. Terraform Workflow 7. Setup 8. Action 9. Cleanup Introduction  A few days ago, I shared my story about creating a Docker image for The Weekly Challenge website in this blog post.
It was a great learning experience for me, I had never done it before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-actions/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  GitHub Actions  1. Introduction 2. Workflow 3. Top Level Keys a) Required Keys b) Optional Keys 4. Event Types 5. Repository Events 6. Job Components a) Required Components b) Optional Components 7. Example a) Proof of Concept Introduction  I have been planning to learn GitHub Actions for a long time. I attended a talk by Dave Cross in 2023 at the Perl Conference in Toronto but when I came back home, I got distracted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Volume</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-volume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-volume/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.       Docker Volume  1. Setup 2. Bind Mount 3. Use of Docker Volume Setup  For this post, we just need docker.
Let’s quickly set up the environment and verify the installation.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-buildx-plugin docker-compose-plugin $ sudo usermod -aG docker $USER  Verify the installation:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.       Docker Compose  1. Setup 2. docker-compose vs docker compose 3. Plan a) Create a Docker Network b) Create the MongoDB Container c) Create the Mongo Express Container d) Verify Containers e) Test Connection 4. Observations 5. Docker Compose 6. Cleanup 7. Conclusion Setup  For this post, we will need docker.
Let’s quickly set up the environment and verify the installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Secret</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.       Dockeri Secret  1. Setup 2. Hard Wired Secrets 3. Environment Variables 4. Env File 5. Swarm Mode Setup  Before we do anything, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have the foundation setup properly.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have docker and docker-compose installed, please follow the steps below. Otherwise, proceed to the next section.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.       Build Docker Image  1. Introduction 2. Journey 3. Setup Introduction  I know the post title is a little vague, what I meant is building docker image for the weekly challenge website.
If you are new to The Weekly Challenge then this is the perfect platform for all geeks who want to use their favourite programming language to solve the two challenges we present every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Large File</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/read-large-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/read-large-file/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.      Read Large File  I remember during my early days, I was asked in one job interview, how would I process a really large text file?.
And I answered, by reading line by line.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t get through the interview, not sure because of my response to the above question.
When I say large file, I mean it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>