<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - Perl5 &amp; Perl6</title>
    <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Perl Weekly Challenge - Perl5 &amp; Perl6</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://perlweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 003</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-003/</guid>
      <description>Last week challenge turned out to be a cakewalk for Perl 6 hackers. This shows my lack of knowledge of Perl 6. I have requested our inhouse Perl 6 experts to share some challenging questions. I already received few and kept in the challenge bank. I will use it in the coming weeks. Credit will be given to the hacker when published. We highly recommend that you submit you solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - Perl Weekly Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first weekly recap of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;.
Apology for the delay, I was supposed to release this blog with the second challenge of the series. I promise next blog is going to be on time.
For the first time ever, the Monday 25th March 2019, was not depressing like any other Monday. Thanks to &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo;, I was so busy following public reactions on Twitter. It was a memorable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perl Weekly Challenge - 002</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-002/</guid>
      <description>It is already time for the second challenge of &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. We have had very positive response so far. We will soon share the review of first challenge. You can send us your solutions by replying the same email that drops the weekly challenge to your inbox. If you are active on twitter then you can DM @PerlWChallenge as well. Or if you have GitHub profile then you can even submit your solutions as PR to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Solution for Challenge - 001</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/philippe-bruhat-challenge-001/</guid>
      <description>This is actually as we received in response to the challenge by Philippe Bruhat. Highly recommended.
Challenge #1 Write a script to replace the character ‘e’ with ‘E’ in the string ‘Perl Weekly Challenge’. Also print the number of times the character ‘e’ found in the string.
 $ perl -E &#39;$_=shift;say y/e/E/;say&#39; &#39;Perl Weekly Challenge&#39; 5 PErl WEEkly ChallEngE  Historical note: y///c is called &amp;ldquo;Abigail&amp;rsquo;s length horror&amp;rdquo; by golfers and obfuscators (couldn&amp;rsquo;t trace where the term came from).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Week a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://perlweeklychallenge.org/blog/a-new-week-a-new-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first task of the &amp;ldquo;Perl Weekly Challenge&amp;rdquo; event. Every Monday, we are going to propose 2 challenges, one aimed at Beginners and another for Experts. However you are free to choose the challenge you fancy. You can even attempt to solve both. As you know the choice of languages are Perl5 and Perl6. You can solve one challenge in Perl5 and other in Perl6, if you like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>