<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 6, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 5 | Day 6 |  The gift is presented by Arne Sommer. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 308. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Challenge #308.1: Count Common You are given two array of strings, @str1 and @str2.
Write a script to return the count of common strings in both arrays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 5, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 4 | Day 5 | Day 6 |  The gift is presented by Matthias Muth. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 307. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Task 1: Check Order You are given an array of integers, @ints.
Write a script to re-arrange the given array in an increasing order and return the indices where it differs from the original array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025/</guid>
      <description>| 2019 | 2020 | 2021 | 2022 | 2023 | 2024 | 2025 |  Here we are, kicking off another Advent season. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to look back and see how far we&amp;rsquo;ve come - and none of it would have been possible without the energy, passion, and teamwork of everyone in Team PWC. Thanks for bringing the magic to life once again!
                        MON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, CUDA, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, Gleam, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 4, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 3 | Day 4 | Day 5 |  The gift is presented by Peter Campbell Smith. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 306. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Task — Odd sum You are given an array of positive integers, @ints. Write a script to return the sum of all possible odd-length subarrays of the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 3, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 2 | Day 3 | Day 4 |  The gift is presented by Jorg Sommrey. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 305. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Alien Primes Task 1: Binary Prefix You are given a binary array. Write a script to return an array of booleans where the partial binary number up to that point is prime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 2, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 1 | Day 2 | Day 3 |  The gift is presented by Dave Jacoby. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 304. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Welcome to Weekly Challenge #304! 304 is many things: A compound number (24 * 19), the area code for West Virginia, a common and corrosion-resistant alloy of stainless steel, (with leading zero) an album by Jewel that Todd in the Shadows calls a Trainwrecord, and an HTTP error code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 1, 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2025-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2025 | Day 1 | Day 2 |  The gift is presented by Ali Moradi. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 303. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2025 from the original post.
 Task #1  We find all 3 variations of digits, and check if it is even, then remove the duplicates:
#!/usr/bin/env perl use strict; use warnings; use Algorithm::Combinatorics qw(variations); use List::Util qw(uniq); use Data::Show; sub three_digits_even{ @{$_[0]} = sort{$a &amp;lt;=&amp;gt; $b} @{$_[0]}; uniq map{join &amp;#39;&amp;#39;,@$_} grep{$_-&amp;gt;[0] &amp;amp;&amp;amp; !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Perl Workshop 2025</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/lpw-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/lpw-2025/</guid>
      <description>For the first time ever, I took my wife and twins to London Perl Workshop. They came not only to see me give a talk, but also to watch me launch my first book, titled &amp;ldquo;Design Patterns in Modern Perl&amp;rdquo;.

The twins were excited to see if their dad was famous. To them, I am a superhero.
The day started with a hiccup—our local train station was closed for some reason, so bus services were provided instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 349</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-349/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-349/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  1. HEADLINES 2. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 3. CONTRIBUTION STATS 4. GUESTS 5. LANGUAGES 6. CENTURION CLUB 7. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 8. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 9. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>