<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Kap, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Docker Compose  For this post, we will need docker.
Setting Up the Environment  Let’s quickly set up the environment and verify the installation.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-buildx-plugin docker-compose-plugin $ sudo usermod -aG docker $USER  Verify the installation:
$ docker --version Docker version 28.0.1, build 068a01e  Edward J. Sabol, on Facebook reminded me that if I am using recent version of docker then I can use the compose sub-command of the docker also in my examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Secret</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Docker Secret Before we do anything, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have the foundation setup properly.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have docker and docker-compose installed, please follow the steps below. Otherwise, proceed to the next section.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-buildx-plugin docker-compose-plugin  Add your user to the docker group to avoid the need to use sudo for every docker command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Build Docker Image I know the post title is a little vague, what I meant is building docker image for the weekly challenge website.
Introduction  If you are new to The Weekly Challenge then this is the perfect platform for all geeks who want to use their favourite programming language to solve the two challenges we present every week. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be an expert in the programming language, as there is always one simple challenge for beginners and a second, more advanced challenge for those with greater experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Large File</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/read-large-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/read-large-file/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Read Large File I remember during my early days, I was asked in one job interview, how would I process a really large text file?.
And I answered, by reading line by line.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t get through the interview, not sure because of my response to the above question.
When I say large file, I mean it.
How about 1GB in size?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git show ...</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-show/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  git show &amp;hellip; I would say, git show, is the most used git command in the life of a programmer after git commit.
Believe it or not, we do so many commits in a day and we peek into a commit if we are investigating an issue.
This is what we do actually: git show &amp;lt;commit_id&amp;gt;, to be precise.
Yeah, so we all know that, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of this post?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 312</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-312/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 313</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-313/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Broken Keys 10. TASK #2: Reverse Letters HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #313 of The Weekly Challenge.
Thank you, Kaushik, for back to back contributions in Perl and blog post.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if noticed this, there is a drop in Raku contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git bisect ...</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-bisect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/git-bisect/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  git bisect &amp;hellip; If you lead life of a programmer, no matter what language you use, you must have used one of the many versioning systems.
CVS was my first introduction to the life saving tool. I think it was early 2000s time period.
I remember a real life incident, I was working as a consultant for a web portal firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promise in Perl</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/promise-in-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/promise-in-perl/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Promise in Perl  Few days ago, I blogged about Future in Perl where I mentioned Future aka Promise.
In this post, I would replicate the behaviour using CPAN modules: Promise::ES6 and AE.
Since Perl believes in the philosophy of TMTOWTDI, so let&amp;rsquo;s implement the most basic pattern of Promiseas below:
fetch() .then(process) .then(save) .then(display) .catch(error);  #!/usr/bin/env perl use v5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>