<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 15, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 14 | Day 15 |  The gift is presented by Lance Wicks. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 221. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 TDD for Good&amp;hellip; strings  One of the things about Test Driven Development (TDD) is that it&amp;rsquo;s something that takes practice. A great way to do that is via the amazing Weekly Challenge which is led by the amazing Mohammad Anwar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 14, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 13 | Day 14 | Day 15 |  The gift is presented by W. Luis Mochan. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 264. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Perl Weekly Challenge 264  Task #1: Greatest English Letter  You are given a string, $str, made up of only alphabetic characters [a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Dc, Elixir, Elm, Emacs Lisp, Erlang, Excel VBA, F#, Factor, Fennel, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, GP, Groovy, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Hy, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, K, Korn Shell, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Maxima, Miranda, Modula 3, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nelua, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 13, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-13/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 12 | Day 13 | Day 14 |  The gift is presented by Bob Lied. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 263. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Don&amp;rsquo;t Sort It, Be Happy  Task #1: Target Index  You are given an array of integers, @ints, and a target element $k. Write a script to return the list of indices in the sorted array where the element is the same as the given target element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 12, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 11 | Day 12 | Day 13 |  The gift is presented by Ali Moradi. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 262. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Weekly Challenge 262  Task #1: Max Positive Negative  You are given an array of integers, @ints. Write a script to return the maximum number of either positive or negative integers in the given array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 11, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-11/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 10 | Day 11 | Day 12 |  The gift is presented by Simon Green. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 261. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 Weekly Challenge 261  Task #1: Element Digit Sum  You are given an array of integers, @ints. Write a script to evaluate the absolute difference between element and digit sum of the given arra  My solution  Given that Perl doesn&amp;rsquo;t care (most of the time) between numbers and strings, this is one of those challenges that is easier to do in Perl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 10, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 9 | Day 10 | Day 11 |  The gift is presented by Robbie Hatley. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 260. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 The Weekly Challenge 260  Task #1: Unique Occurrences  You are given an array of integers, @ints. Write a script to return 1 if the number of occurrences of each value in the given array is unique or 0 otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 9, 2024</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2024-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2024 | Day 8 | Day 9 | Day 10 |  The gift is presented by James Smith. Today he is talking about his solution to The Weekly Challenge - 263. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2024 from the original post.
 The Weekly Challenge - 263  Task #1: Target Index  You are given an array of integers, @ints and a target element $k. Write a script to return the list of indices in the sorted array where the element is same as the given target element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - The Weekly Challenge - 298</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-298/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/recap-challenge-298/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. STAR CONTRIBUTORS 03. CONTRIBUTION STATS 04. GUESTS 05. LANGUAGES 06. CENTURION CLUB 07. DAMIAN CONWAY&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 08. ANDREW SHITOV&amp;rsquo;s CORNER 09. PERL SOLUTIONS 10. RAKU SOLUTIONS 11. PERL &amp;amp; RAKU SOLUTIONS HEADLINES  Thank you Team PWC for your continuous support and encouragement.
STAR CONTRIBUTORS  Following members shared solutions to both tasks in Perl and Raku as well as blogged about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - 299</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-299/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/perl-weekly-challenge-299/</guid>
      <description>TABLE OF CONTENTS  01. HEADLINES 02. SPONSOR 03. RECAP 04. PERL REVIEW 05. RAKU REVIEW 06. CHART 07. NEW MEMBERS 08. GUESTS 09. TASK #1: Replace Words 10. TASK #2: Word Search HEADLINES  Welcome to the Week #299 of The Weekly Challenge.
Advent Calendar 2024  Day 1: Leaping from Tree to Tree as They Float Down the Mighty Rivers of British Columbia by Dave Jacoby. Day 2: Special Zeroes by Jorg Sommrey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>