<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/c/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C on The Weekly Challenge - Perl &amp; Raku</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/c/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Challenge - Guest Contributions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/guest-contribution/</guid>
      <description>As you know, The Weekly Challenge, primarily focus on Perl and Raku. During the Week #018, we received solutions to The Weekly Challenge - 018 by Orestis Zekai in Python. It was pleasant surprise to receive solutions in something other than Perl and Raku. Ever since regular team members also started contributing in other languages like Ada, APL, Awk, BASIC, Bash, Bc, Befunge-93, Bourne Shell, BQN, Brainfuck, C3, C, CESIL, Chef, COBOL, Coconut, C Shell, C++, Clojure, Crystal, D, Dart, Elm, Erlang, Excel VBA, Fish, Forth, Fortran, Gembase, GNAT, Go, Haskell, Haxe, HTML, Idris, IO, J, Janet, Java, JavaScript, Julia, Kotlin, Lisp, Logo, Lua, M4, Miranda, MMIX, Mumps, Myrddin, Nim, Nix, Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent Calendar - December 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2020-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/advent-calendar-2020-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Advent Calendar 2020 | Day 15 | Day 16 | Day 17 |  The gift is presented by Yet Ebreo. Today he is talking about his solution to the task Calling C function of &amp;ldquo;The Weekly Challenge - 029&amp;rdquo;. This is re-produced for Advent Calendar 2020 from the original post by Yet Ebreo.
  Write a script to demonstrate calling a C function. It could be any user defined or standard C function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>