<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aws on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in aws on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS KMS Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-kms-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS KMS Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Using aws 3. Using Python 4. Using Perl Introduction  This post is in continuation of the last post where we explored the AWS S3 Encryption.
In this post, I would like to talk about encryption using AWS Key Management Service.
AWS Key Management Service (KMS) is a managed service that enables easy encryption of data using cryptographic keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS S3 Encryption</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/aws-s3-encryption/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI. AWS S3 Encryption  1. Introduction 2. Types of S3 Encryption 3. Server-Side Encryption (SSE) 4. Client-Side Encryption (CSE) 5. AWS Managed Keys (SSE-S3) 6. Using aws 7. Using Python 8. Using Perl Introduction  A week ago, I wrote a blog post about AWS S3 using the LocalStack platform. It was originally intended to cover just the basic operations. However, a few days later, I updated the post to include object versioning in AWS S3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LocalStack with AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/localstack-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using Leonardo AI.  1. Introduction 2. Setup awscli 3. Setup LocalStack 4. Make Bucket 5. List Buckets 6. Upload File 7. Download File 8. Delete File 9. List Bucket 10. Remove Bucket 11. S3 with Python 12. S3 with Perl 13. What next? Introduction  Recently I got the opportunity to work with AWS S3 at work.
For this I wanted to brush up my knowledge as last I played with it was an year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>