<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Secret</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Docker Secret Before we do anything, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have foundation setup properly.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have docker and docker-compose installed then please follow the steps below otherwise move to the next section.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-buildx-plugin docker-compose-plugin  Add your user to the Docker group to avoid the need to use sudo on every Docker command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  Build Docker Image I know the post title is a little vague, what I meant is building docker image for the weekly challenge website.
Introduction  If you are new to The Weekly Challenge then this is the perfect platform for all geeks who want to use their favourite programming language to solve the two challenges we present every week. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be an expert in the programming language, as there is always one simple challenge for beginners and a second, more advanced challenge for those with greater experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>