<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on The Weekly Challenge</title>
    <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on The Weekly Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theweeklychallenge.org/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform with Docker</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/terraform-docker/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Terraform with Docker  1. Introduction 2. Objectives 3. What is Terraform? 4. Why Terraform? 5. Terraform Configuration File 6. Terraform Workflow 7. Setup 8. Action 9. Cleanup Introduction  A few days ago, I shared my story about creating a Docker image for The Weekly Challenge website in this blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/github-actions/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.  GitHub Actions  1. Introduction 2. Workflow 3. Top Level Keys a) Required Keys b) Optional Keys 4. Event Types 5. Repository Events 6. Job Components a) Required Components b) Optional Components 7. Example a) Proof of Concept Introduction  I have been planning to learn GitHub Actions for a long time. I attended a talk by Dave Cross in 2023 at the Perl Conference in Toronto but when I came back home, I got distracted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Volume</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-volume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-volume/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Docker Volume  1. Setup 2. Bind Mount 3. Use of Docker Volume Setup  For this post, we just need docker.
Let’s quickly set up the environment and verify the installation.
$ sudo apt update $ sudo apt install -y docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-buildx-plugin docker-compose-plugin $ sudo usermod -aG docker $USER  Verify the installation:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Docker Compose  1. Setup 2. docker-compose vs docker compose 3. Plan a) Create a Docker Network b) Create the MongoDB Container c) Create the Mongo Express Container d) Verify Containers e) Test Connection 4. Observations 5. Docker Compose 6. Cleanup 7. Conclusion Setup  For this post, we will need docker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Secret</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/docker-secret/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Dockeri Secret  1. Setup 2. Hard Wired Secrets 3. Environment Variables 4. Env File 5. Swarm Mode Setup  Before we do anything, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have the foundation setup properly.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have docker and docker-compose installed, please follow the steps below. Otherwise, proceed to the next section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theweeklychallenge.org/blog/build-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: Image is generated using FREE version of ChatGPT.            Build Docker Image  1. Introduction 2. Journey 3. Setup Introduction  I know the post title is a little vague, what I meant is building docker image for the weekly challenge website.
If you are new to The Weekly Challenge then this is the perfect platform for all geeks who want to use their favourite programming language to solve the two challenges we present every week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>